<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<EVENTS>
    <TECHNICAL>
        <CSE>
            <CSE_PAPER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Paper Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True
                    <br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Suggested Topics</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. Cyber Crime and  Security <br></br>
                    2. Wireless Sensor Networks <br></br>
										3. Big Data Analytics<br></br>
										4. Cloud Computing <br></br>
										5. Machine learning<br></br>
										6. Internet of Things<br></br>
									  7. Web Technologies
                    <br></br>
                    <br></br>
										<b>About:</b>
										<br></br>
										One has to come up with your project that can be presented visually that aims to introduce the latest and innovative designs and models, what not you can present any of your models provided they are impressive sparks of innovation.
                    <br></br><br></br>
										<b>Rules:</b>                    
                    <br></br>
                    1. Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>
                    2. Teams willing to participate should send their abstracts.<br></br>
                    3. Paper should be in IEEE format( the format can be downloaded from Internet) and abstract should be of 250 words<br></br>
                    4. Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail.<br></br>
                    5. Each team will be given 8min for presentation and 2min for queries<br></br>
										6.Selected teams have to bring their hardcopies in a folder on the day of events.
                    <br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Presentation:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. The presentation should be in .PPT format.<br></br>
                    2. Selected teams have to bring all their documents in a CD with 1 hardcopy of abstract and 2 hard copies of Complete paper.<br></br>
                    3. Video clippings and voice recordings are not allowed.<br></br>
										4. The paper should be in IEEE format as PDF and should contain 5 - 8 pages<br></br>
										5. CD should contain PPT + ABSTRACT + PAPER REPORT which should be submitted on the day of event.
                    <br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>csepaper2016@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT> 
                    Contact :
                    <br></br>
                    V.SONICA SUPRIYA<br></br>
                    9290958114<br></br>
										sonicasupriya95@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </CSE_PAPER>
            <CSE_POSTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True
										<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Suggested Topics :</b><br></br>
                     1. Cyber Crime and  Security <br></br>
                    2. Wireless Sensor Networks <br></br>
										3. Big Data Analytics<br></br>
										4. Cloud Computing <br></br>
										5. Machine learning<br></br>
										6. Internet of Things<br></br>
									  7. Web Technologies
										<br></br> <br></br>
                    <b>Rules :</b><br></br>
                    1. Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>
										2. Teams willing to participate should send their abstracts.<br></br>
										3. Abstract should be in pdf or doc format.<br></br>
										4. Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail.<br></br>
										5. Each team will be given 8min for presentation and 2min for queries.
                    <br></br><br></br> 
                    <b>Presentation :</b><br></br>  
                    1. Teams selected need to bring soft copies and 2 printed posters.<br></br>
                    2. The poster should be of A3 Size and the soft copy should be in PNG format. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
										<b>Judging Criteria:</b><br></br>
										The team would be judged on <br></br>
										a) Poster Making<br></br>
										b) Content of the poster.<br></br>
										c) Presentation Skills.<br></br>
										d) Answering Queries.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Poster Making:</b><br></br>             
                    1. The poster must be neat and legible.<br></br>
                    2. Apt background should be selected so that words are legible.<br></br>
                    3. A picture should speak the content of a 1000 words.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the members have to send their soft copies to "<i>yadavpav2726@gmail.com</i>"<br /></b> 

                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact :</b><br></br>
									NAKKA.PAVAN YADAV<br></br>
									8790094001<br></br>
									yadavpav2726@gmail.com<br></br>
								</CONTACT>
            </CSE_POSTER>
            <CSE_PROJECT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Project Expo</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                     <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True
										<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Suggested Topics :</b><br></br>
                    1. Cyber Crime and  Security <br></br>
                    2. Wireless Sensor Networks <br></br>
										3. Big Data Analytics<br></br>
										4. Cloud Computing <br></br>
										5. Machine learning<br></br>
										6. Internet of Things<br></br>
									  7. Web Technologies<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b><br></br>
                    1. Working models only.<br></br>
                    2. Ready-made kits are not acceptable.<br></br>
                    3. On-board, off-board source can be used.<br></br>
                    4. Applications of your model should be shown.<br></br>
                    5. Project may be movable or stable.<br></br>
                    6. Model should be unique.<br></br>
                    7. No two similar projects are allowed. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judging Criteria</b><br></br>
                    1. Degree of Innovation- 20%<br></br>
                    2. Design &amp; Realisation-20%<br></br>
                    3. Performance-30%<br></br>
                    4. Content-20%<br></br>
                    5. Usefulness/Application-10% <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Expo:</b><br></br>
										All entries will be allocated exhibition space where the PROJECT  will remain throughout the day. 
									Contestants are to man the exhibits at all times and should be available to answer questions from judges and members
									of the public. Prize winners will be announced at the end of the day of competition. Decision of judges if final. 
										<br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>modadugup@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                    <br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact:</b><br></br>
									M.PREMNATH<br></br>
									9912459019<br></br>
									modadugup@gmail.com<br></br>
								</CONTACT>
            </CSE_PROJECT>
            <DIGTHEBUG>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Dig the Bug</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    A  code breaking game.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 1:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    It is an group event...... 9 problems..... numerous bugs.... only one objective - make the code do what it should! There are so many *bugs*, and we bet if they squash one and hear closely enough,will be promoted to next round. Time boxing places major role.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 2:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    In this round same process is followed as in first round,but time limit will be reduced and complexity will be increased.
                    The aim of the event is to get ahead, armed with your creativity and resourcefulness. The event is not a general knowledge quiz and no trivia knowledge would be expected from the participants.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules for preliminary and main rounds:</b>
                    <br></br>

                    1.	There will be two members in each team.
                    <br></br>
                    2.	Each team is allotted 30 minutes.<br></br>
                    3.	There will be 10 levels in all.<br></br>
                    4.	One can go to next level only when the present code will be cracked.<br></br>
                    5.	Any team found asking an answer or helping other team will be disqualified at that time only.<br></br>
                    6.	The team first completing the game or reaching the maximum level will be called for the finals.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judgement process:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Participants who clears all bugs and gets output will be given first priority,else participants who are left with minimum number of bugs will be promoted to next round.<br></br>
                    
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact :
                   <br></br>
              			S. Swathi Bindu <br></br>8790633550<br></br><i>swathichowdary@gmail.com</i>      
							</CONTACT>
            </DIGTHEBUG>
            <PIXELLATE>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>PIXELLATE</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Pixellate is a contest in which participants are asked to design graphics using the given set of  images and other resources. The event is divided into two rounds. The first is an elimination round in which a short design problem will be given. The second round will comprise of a designing challenge based on the given theme followed by a presentation through which the designer conveys what the design means to him/her.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>The designs will be judged on the following criteria:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	Skill<br></br>
                    •	Creativity<br></br>
                    •	Message/Thought behind the design 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	A maximum of two participants are allowed per team.<br></br>
                    •	Round one will be of 35 minutes and round two will of 1 hour 15 minutes duration.<br></br>
                    •	No external reference is allowed, only the given set of resources must be used. <br></br>
                    •	In case of tie, preference will be given to the criteria mentioned above in decreasing order of weight age. <br></br>
                    •	The decision of judges would be final and binding.<br></br>
                    •	The designs must not contain abusive language, racial slurs or hateful remarks against any religion, cast or community. Event manager reserves the right to disqualify any team if any section of the content is deemed inappropriate. 
                    
                 </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT><b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    N.Deepti <br></br>
									 9493437505<br></br>deeptinimmagadda2000@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </PIXELLATE>
            <LOGOQUIZ>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>LOGO Quiz</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Participants have to guess the electronic components or inventors based on the clues given.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round1:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	A total of 4 clues will be given(pictures or inventors or logos).<br></br>
                    •	Participants should identify the logo and answer the software /company name related to logo
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 2:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	In this round, logos are given in a jumbled manner and some questions are given aside.<br></br>
                    •	Questions will be asked based on the ‘connection’ between the pictures/logos<br></br>
                    •	Finally they need to match the logos with questions.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	Only one participant is allowed,not in a group.<br></br>
                    •	No one should interrupt other participants while answering.<br></br>
                    •	No usage of internet or mobile phones.
                   
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                   <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    K.Pankaj Sai Gupta<br></br>9951694555<br></br>pankaj.sai.555@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </LOGOQUIZ>
            <WEBCRAFT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>WEB Craft</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Description :</b><br></br>
										This is a Website Design event in which the students will be asked to design a web based interface. It aims to highlight the creative and programming capabilities of the students.<br></br> 
										The work will be judged on the basis of (with weightage) :
                    <br></br>									
                    •	Site Navigation, User friendliness (40%)<br></br>
                    •	Presentation, Color Scheme, Attractiveness (35%)<br></br>
                    An ultimate web designing competition to show creativity in front of the world.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>First Round:</b><br></br>
                    Questions on web programming and latest updates in web design development. TOP 20 will move to round 2 .<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Second Round:</b><br></br>
                    Participant need to design a web page or set of web pages in 30min and winners are announced based on the innovativeness and art of design by judges
									<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules and Regulation:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1.	No usage of gadgets/external sources during designing.<br></br>
                    2.	No interference of other person while one is designing.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Team:</b><br></br>									
                    2 persons per team
                    <br></br>
                    Minimum requirements: HTML,CSS
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judgement procedure:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. Top 20teams with higher scores in the first round will move to the second round.<br></br>
										2. Team consuming least time and having more innovativeness in the design will be the winner in the final round.<br></br><br></br>
                   
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
										<b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Y.Avinash Reddy <br></br> 9700438898<br></br><i>avinashreddy23@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </WEBCRAFT>
            <FALGO>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Finding ALGO !!!</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    ‘Finding ALGO!!!’ is structured as a two tiered competition with participants competing in teams of two.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND1:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    The first round sees the teams submitting solutions in pseudo code to 10 problems, with the best teams going forward to the second round of the competition. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND2:</b>									
                    <br></br>
                    The selected teams then battle it out in a half an hour long coding session, the winning teams being awarded with an attractive prizes, apart from the glory of being crowned the victors of the prestigious event.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b>									
                    <br></br>
                    •	Participants should not use any gadgets.<br></br>
                    •	Every participant should have minimum knowledge of C,DS, ADS.<br></br>
                    •	No participant is allowed to help other participant.<br></br>
                    •	Team members should not exceed time limit.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judgment process:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. Based on best time complexity, various outcomes of algorithm, Logic provided and number of lines of code then the team that submitted algorithm in less time will be promoted to next round.<br></br>
										2. The team which gives outcome in least time can be awarded as winners.<br></br><br></br>
                   
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact:</b>  
									<br></br>
                    A.Sai Srivatsa<br></br> 8985039355<br></br><i>vatsaadiraju@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </FALGO>
            <BTF>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>BACK-TO-FRONT ENDS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    We have a session of 30 questions on  C,C++,HTML,CSS,DBMS  rearranged in 4 sets. Participants are given  minimum amount of time to solve those questions. Finally, top 3 winners will be given chance to come out with ideas that are useful to society and gifts are awarded
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND1:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	Participants are given 30 questions based on topics mentioned above.<br></br>
                    •	The participants who scored more will be selected for next round.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>ROUND2:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	Selected participants are asked to give their best IDEA’s for STARTUP’s.<br></br>
                    •	Best ideas will be selected by judges and awarded.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    •	Idea must be related to CSE.<br></br>
                    •	Must be implementable.<br></br>
                    •	Describe the idea for more than five minutes<br></br>
                    •	Analyze the specifications and requirements of the idea.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Judgement process:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. The participants who answers more number of questions correct will be promoted to next round.<br></br>
										2. In final round based on idea exhibited and real time analysis (reach out posssibility for no. of people) can be deciding factor of winners.<br></br>
                    3. Winner will be decided by judges based on innovativeness and impact on society.<br></br><br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
             <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact:</b>  
									<br></br>
                    Ch.Venkata Rana Pratap<br></br>9701711258<br></br><i>rana.hansome@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </BTF>
            <SWITCH_CODING>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="cse.php">CSE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Switch Coding</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Description:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Switch coding is a unique blend of programming and teamwork .It requires two people to code the given list of programs while taking turns and switching with his/her team-mate every two minutes. The programmer's team-mate is not allowed to see his partner progress until it is his turn, nor he is allowed to communicate with him. Each team is allotted 90 mins to code their particular list of programs. It requires extensive teamwork and coordination among the participants as the other participant has to start off from where the other left off. The teams are judged based on the number of successful programs completed. The event will comprise of 2 rounds after which the top ten teams qualify for the final round on the second day. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules and Regulation:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1.	No usage of gadgets/external sources during coding.<br></br>
                    2.	No interference of other person while one is coding.<br></br>
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round Details:  </b>
                    <br></br>
                    The event will comprise of 2 rounds. Every team need to code for the given problem by following the rules as specified in the description in both the rounds. The top ten teams which took least time to complete the program in first round  will qualify for the second round on the second day.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Team:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    2 persons per team
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judgement procedure:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    The Teams who complete the coding in lesser time will be forwarded to the next round. Team consuming least time in the final round will be the winner.
                    <br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                 <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact:</b>  
									<br></br>
                   K.Ashok<br></br>9492090429<br></br><i>ashok.karanam1996@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </SWITCH_CODING>            
        </CSE>
        <ECE>
            <ECE_PAPER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Paper Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                   <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br><br></br>
 The main motto should be for healthy development of INDIA in all aspects. 
<br></br><br></br>
<b>SUGGESTED TOPICS:</b>
 <br></br>
1. MEMES<br></br>
2. VLSI <br></br>
3. EMBEDDED SYSTEMS<br></br>
4. COMMUNICATION<br></br>
5. SIGNAL PROCESSING<br></br><br></br>

									<b>RULES:</b>
<br></br>
1. Team size should not exceed two members.<br></br>
2. Abstract should be in pdf or .doc format.<br></br>
3. Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail.<br></br>
4. Paper should be in IEEE format.<br></br>
									<br></br>
<b>PRESENTATION:</b>
<br></br>
1. Presentation should be in .ppt format.<br></br>
2. Teams selected are required to bring a softcopy and 2 hard copies of complete paper to presentation.<br></br>
3. Presentation should not exceed 8 min.<br></br>
<br></br>
									<b>JUDGEMENT CRITERIA:</b><br></br>
1. Technical content of the paper.<br></br>
2. Presentation skills.<br></br>
3. Answering Queries.<br></br>

									
										<b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>divisushma95@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    DIVI SUSHMA
                    <br></br>Contact Number : 9030828899<br></br>
                    Email Id : divisushma95@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ECE_PAPER>
            <ECE_POSTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									 <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br><br></br>
 The main motto should be for healthy development of INDIA in all aspects. <br></br><br></br>
									<b>SUGGESTED TOPICS:</b>
<br></br>1. ADVANCEMENT IN TECHNOLOGY SUPPORTING HUMAN LIFE AND WELFARE
<br></br>2. CONNECTING PEOPLE WITH SMART TECHNOLOGY
<br></br>3. ADVANCED WIRELSS COMMUNICATIONS
<br></br>4. OLED-(ORGANIC LIGHT EMITTING DIODE)
<br></br>5. CRYPTOGRAPHY
<br></br><br></br>Rural people face problems with Energy management. No proper power supplies in rural areas make people to face problems. Using the following 
<br></br>1. Antennas
<br></br>2. Mobile Communication
<br></br>3. Satellite Communication
<br></br><br></br>Prepare a project related to Energy Management and that should be efficient. Cost should not exceed 15,000/-<br></br>
Every participant should come up with their prototype model of their project which would be helpful for sustainable rural development.<br></br>	<br></br>
								
									<b>Note: All the members have to send their soft copies to "<i> ksaidheeraj@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    K.SAI DHEERAJ
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9703590031<br></br>
                    Email Id : ksaidheeraj@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ECE_POSTER>
            <ECE_PROJECT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>PROJECT EXHIBITION</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									 <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br><br></br>
 The main motto should be for healthy development of INDIA in all aspects. <br></br><br></br>
									<b>SUGGESTED TOPICS:</b><br></br>
									1. ADVANCEMENT IN TECHNOLOGY SUPPORTING HUMAN LIFE AND WELFARE<br></br>
									2. CONNECTING PEOPLE WITH SMART TECHNOLOGY<br></br>
									3. ADVANCED WIRELSS COMMUNICATIONS<br></br>
									4. OLED-(ORGANIC LIGHT EMITTING DIODE)<br></br>
									5.	CRYPTOGRAPHY<br></br><br></br>

                    Rural people face problems with Energy management. No proper power supplies in rural areas make people to face problems. Using the following 
                    <br></br>1. Antennas
                    <br></br>2.Mobile Communication
                    <br></br>3.Satellite Communication
                    <br></br>Prepare a project related to Energy Management and that should be efficient. Cost should not exceed 15,000/-
                    <br></br>Every participant should come up with their prototype model of their project which would be helpful for sustainable rural development.	
                    <br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>vjagadeesh1996@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    U.JAGADEESH
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9133174080<br></br>
                    Email Id : vjagadeesh1996@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ECE_PROJECT>
            <EMBEDDED>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>EMBEDDED APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Participants have to build an autonomous robot which can follow a white line and keep track of directions while going through the maze. The bot has to analyse the path in the dry run and has to go through the maze from one corner to the other in minimum possible time.
										<br></br><br></br>
										<b>Round 1 :</b><br></br>
										Code development and bot assembly.<br></br>
										Dumb run (just needs to follow a line doesn't have any specific targets)
										<br></br><br></br>
										<b>Round 2 :</b><br></br>
Smart run (bot has read the maze and find the shortest path without any human contact)<br></br>
The first part of smart run is the dry run. In this part the bot must start from the start zone and find its way to reach the End zone of the arena. The bot will be given a maximum of 3 minutes to reach that point. The bot has to give a signal by glowing a LED as soon as it sense it block. The bot has to follow an algorithm to find its path to reach end zone and bot can store the turns in its memory to explore the shortest path during second part of journey. <br></br>
The second part consists of starting from the start zone again and find its way to the end zone it best possible path by using the path that was stored in first part. The bot will get maximum of 2 minutes for it to complete this part. The end zone has a 100mm x 100mm x 100mm block that indicates the ending of the path for the bot. <br></br>
<br></br><b>Note:
Participants are expected to bring their own robot kit. Kits will be provided by the organizers for those participants that don't poses their own on a deposit of Rs. 50/-</b>
<br></br><br></br>
1. The game field consists of an arena having dimensions 2310 mm X 2310 mm.<br></br>
 2. The arena is composed of random paths made up of white strips. <br></br>
3. Distance between two adjacent lines is 300mm.<br></br>
4. The width of all white stripes will be 30mm. <br></br>
5. The autonomous bot must fit into the box of dimension 220 mm X 220 mm X 220 mm<br></br>
6.  Both must have on board power supply.<br></br>
7. Participants with their personal robot have to get their bots inspected by organizers prior to event<br></br>
8. Participant who received the bot from organizer have to submit them back to the organizer at the end of each round.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    N.JAYA DEVI<br></br>
                    9703590031<br></br>
                    vjagadeesh1996@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </EMBEDDED>
            <DIGI_DAS>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>DIGI-GAME</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    In this event we are going to have fun with digital circuits.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 1:-</b><br></br>
                    Questions regarding basics of digital circuits will be asked orally.<br></br>
                    Selected students will be promoted to round-2.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 2:-</b><br></br>
                    Students will be asked to solve the logic circuits.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 3:-</b><br></br>
                    Selected students in round-2 will be asked to solve higher level of questions.<br></br>
                    So are you ready to take the ride? Well, what are you waiting for? Get ready to cross swords with Digi-Das.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    A.MAANYA SAI<br></br>
                    96187594968<br></br>
                    allurimaanyasai@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </DIGI_DAS>
            <CREATOR_CORNER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>CREATOR’S CORNER</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    This event tests the creativity of the participant. The event consists of mainly three rounds.<br></br>
                    In the first round we show them a certain products of Indian market and ask them to write a caption for it and who ever writes the exciting captions they are promoted to the next round.<br></br>
                    In the second round we play a part of movie that is movie clip without audio and ask them to write about the scene in few lines they have to use here their creativity here and whoever has written most apt description they are selected for the next round.<br></br>
                    In the third round they are given 10 words and finally they have to frame a paragraph of meaningful story with including all those words. The story should contain humor and also an end. Whoever has written the best story he/she is awarded the first prize winner and appropriately the second and third prizes are given.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    V.THANMAYEE<br></br>
                    9493629659<br></br>
                    vankayalapatithanmayee@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </CREATOR_CORNER>
            <GALAXY>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>CIRCUIT GALAXY</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Paticipants will be given with circuit diagrams and the function of that circuit<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 1 :</b><br></br>
                    <b>Task 1</b><br></br>
                    Analize of the circut and specify the requried parameters<br></br>
                    <b>Task 2</b><br></br>
                    A specific function will the given and participants have to reyalise the circuit<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 2 :</b><br></br>
                    <b>Task 1</b><br></br>
                    A mock circuit will  be given along with specific task  for which the participant has to achieve the with the least amount of modifications possible<br></br>
                    <b>Task 2</b><br></br>
                    Participants have to display the advantage of the circuit they realized in round 1 task 2 with proper explanation
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    P.NAGA DIVYA<br></br>
                    9246779946<br></br>
                    divyapothuri@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </GALAXY>
            <TECHNICAL_QUIZ>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ece.php">ECE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>TECHNICAL QUIZ</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                   A quiz is a form of game or mind sport in which the players attempt to answer questions correctly. A quiz is also a brief assessment used in education and similar fields to measure growth in knowledge,
									abilities or skills. This event tests the basics of the students regarding various aspects and fields of electronics and communication engineering.<br></br><br></br>
This quiz not only tests the clarity of basic concepts in chemical engineering and chemistry but also the analytical skills and logical reasoning skills essential for an engineer
									to analyze a problem critically and get quick solutions. You could expect many new types of questions this time. This edition will feature a whole
									array of stimulating new rounds and questions. Do come and test your mettle here and attempt to get crowned champions of quizzing, or simply witness the coronation.
									You are sure to learn tons of interesting facts.

                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
											<b>Chief Dept. Co-ordinator</b><br></br>
                    Sk. Sai Hassanbaba<br></br>
                    8341850119<br></br>
                    hassanbaba76@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </TECHNICAL_QUIZ>   
        </ECE>
        <EEE>
            <EEE_PAPER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Paper Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                   <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Topics</b><br></br>
										1. Smart grid<br></br>
										2. Power electronics in transportation(road,aerospace,marine and railway vehicles,electric and hybrid vehicles)<br></br>
										3. Power electronics in electrical energy systems(generation,transmissio,distribution,smartgrid,technologies,renewable energy sources)<br></br>
										4. Active filtering and unity power factor collection.<br></br>
										5. Semi conductor devices modelling,packing and integration.<br></br>
										6. Power qulaity  and harmonics.<br></br>
										7. Distributed generation.<br></br>
										8. Electricity market and power syatem economics.<br></br>
										9. Industrial automation.<br></br>
                    *Innovative topics can also be presented.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b><br></br> 
                    1. Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>
                    2. Abstract should be in pdf or doc format.<br></br>
                    3. ￼Complete details of team members should be mentioned in the ￼abstract and modifications of member names will not be ￼entertained<br></br>
                    4. Presenters should first get their unique ids by registering in Samyak website.<br></br>
                    5. Interested teams are required to send their abstracts to ...(MAIL ID)...with the subject as PPT-(samyak id’s of team members) Ex: PPT-SMYK1234,SMYK5678.<br></br>
                    6. Deadline to send abstract is mentioned below.<br></br>
                    7. Selected teams will be informed through e-mail.<br></br>
                    8. Selected teams should send their paper in PDF IEEE format before the deadline prescribed.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Presentation</b><br></br>
										1. The presentation should be in .PPT or .PPTX format.<br></br>
                    2. Teams selected are required to bring a soft copy by CD and 2 hard copies of complete paper to the presentation.<br></br>
                    3. Video clippings and voice recordings are not allowed.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>vijaya.bharathi95@gmail.com</i>" </b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>	
                    A.VIJAYA BHARATHI
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9441445548<br></br>
                    Email Id : vijaya.bharathi95@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </EEE_PAPER>
            <EEE_POSTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                     <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Topics</b><br></br>
                    1. Renewable Energy Resources<br></br>
                    2. Nanotechnology<br></br>
                    3. Smart Grid<br></br>
                    4. Power Quality<br></br>
                    5. Advances in Power Systems<br></br>
                    6. SCADA<br></br>
                    7. PLC<br></br>
                    8. Micro Grids<br></br>
                    9. Industrial Control of Power Electronics<br></br>
                    10. Intelligent Control of Power Electronic Drives<br></br>
                    11. Power Quality Improvement using Multi-Level Inverters<br></br>
                    12. FACTS Controllers<br></br>
                    13. Advances in Power Converter Topologies<br></br>
                    *Innovative topics can also be presented.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>
                    2. Abstract should be in pdf or doc format.<br></br>
                    3. ￼Complete details of team members should be mentioned in the ￼abstract and modifications of member names will not be ￼entertained<br></br>
                    4. Presenters should first get their unique ids by registering in Samyak website.<br></br>
                    5. Interested teams are required to send their abstracts to ...(MAIL ID)...with the subject as PST-(samyak id’s of team members) Ex: PST-SMYK1234,SMYK5678.<br></br>
                    6. Deadline to send abstract is mentioned below.<br></br>
                    7. Selected teams will be informed through e-mail.<br></br>
                    8. Selected teams should send their poster in PNG format before the deadline prescribed.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Presentation</b><br></br>
										1. Teams selected need to bring a soft copy in CD and &amp; the printed poster.<br></br>
										2. The poster should be of A3 size and the soft copy should be in PNG format.<br></br><br></br>
									<b>Note: All the members have to send their soft copies to "<i>saikalyan67@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    P.KALYAN<br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9701877318<br></br>
                    Email Id : saikalyan67@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </EEE_POSTER>
            <EEE_PROJECT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Project Expo</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									  <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br><br></br>
                    It is the presentation of projects. The students need to present their project to judges followed by queries posted by the judges. Judge will select best project and will be awarded. In this event the participant has to come up with a problem faced by the people. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judging criteria:</b>
                    <br></br> 1. The one who comes with a problem faced by people with a better solution is preferred. <br></br>2. Decisions of judges will be the final. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b> Rules:</b>
                    <br></br> 1.  Batch should contain 1 or 2 members only.<br></br> 2. Any other equipment required for their project should bring by their own (only power supplies will be provided). <br></br>3. Participants should bring the softcopy and hardcopy about their project. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b> It should contain:</b> 
                    <br></br><u>Introduction : - </u><br></br>1. Circuit diagrams and program ( if any programmable device are included)<br></br>2. Explanation about working of the project Application
                    <br></br><u>Future scope : - </u><br></br>3. Presentation of report is appreciated (Not Mandatory)<br></br>4. Student must be able to explain about his project to the visitor and answer the questions posed by the judges. <br></br><br></br>
									<b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>sandeep.polina@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    P.SANDEEP
                    <br></br>Contact Number : 8897903525<br></br>
                    Email Id : sandeep.polina@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </EEE_PROJECT>
            <TECH_TALK>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Tech Talk</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>INSPIRE TO INNOVATE</b><br></br>
                    A lot has been said about the “Make In India” program initiated by PM Modi, which aims at transforming nation’s fate towards new horizons.But does Modi’s mission to revive India is growing consistently? The announcement of the “Make In India” program might have brought a smile upon every local manufacturer in India but at the same time, there are some dark spots that are hindering in the process of development of this program.<br></br>
                    Every country is very much blessed with adequate amounts of ‘raw material’ but lack of proper utilization of those leads them to degrade their rank in the world chart, same with our Country. Inspite of abundant resources we are depending on other countries. Is India meant for only importing goods? Can’t we export anything? Can’t we stand tall in the world chart rankings? Is there no potential in us? What are the problems we are facing?<br></br>
                    Suggest remedial measures to overcome these problems. As an entrepreneur one has to gain potential to solve such problems and make their country to top the chart. Is government sole responsible for this situation in our country? Nah, don’t push everything on government. Even it’s trying hard for the same, Just like us. But it needs support and back up. So, c’mon let’s put our ideas together and solve this problem and make our country feel proud of us.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b><br></br>
                    1. Team should not exceed 2 members( Individuals can also participated)<br></br>
                    2. You can use the help of PPT or any medium to express your ideas.<br></br>
                    3. Each participant is given 8 minutes time to express his idea.<br></br>
                    4. The decision of the jury team at any instant will be final.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>For any queries mailus at "<i>eswarsai.veesam@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    V.ESWARSAI
                    <br></br>Contact Number : 7661947776<br></br>
                    Email Id : eswarsai.veesam@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </TECH_TALK>
            <E_PUZZLE>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>ELECTRIC PUZZLE</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Round I: (Assembling puzzle)</b>
                    <br></br>
                    In this round the student will be asked to solve the given puzzle.<br></br>
										By solving that puzzle they have to get electrical word. Time limit will be given to each word.<br></br>
										Teams which complete the puzzle in less time will be promoted to next round.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Round 2: (Building electrical words)</b>
                    <br></br>In this round students are asked to pick a slip which contains alphabet.<br></br>
										They have to build electrical words for that particular alphabet with in specified time.<br></br>
										Teams which builds more number of words within given time will be promoted to next round.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Round 3:(Matching) </b><br></br>
										In this final round we will have the match the following.<br></br>
										The participant have to match the correct option for the given technical words with in the time specified.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>RULES:</b>
                    <br></br> 1. Team should not exceed two members. <br></br>2.Any team violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competition <br></br>3. The decision taken by the Faculty and event co-ordinator will be final.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>For any queries mailus at "<i>kavyapangi09@gmail.com	</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    P.KAVYA
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9492274088<br></br>
                    Email Id : kavyapangi09@gmail.com	
                </CONTACT>
            </E_PUZZLE>
            <STOP_THINK>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>STOP THINKING &amp; START DOING</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>
                        Round I:  (Make a sense)</b>
                    <br></br>In this round the participants has to determine the correct path of the wires for which the bulb is connected to the switch.<br></br>
										The participant’s intelligence will be tested to the maximum extent regarding to his basics in physics.<br></br>
										He has to route the correct path for the bulbs from the switch’s provided.<br></br>
										Evenly his senses has to work out well for getting the correct path for the bulb and the switch.<br></br>
										If he determines the correct path for the bulb and the switch relation, he is promoted to the next round. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round II:  (Get it correct)</b>
                    <br></br>In this round the participant will be given with the electrical component diagrams pasted over a thermocol sheets.<br></br>
										He/she has to connect it with the wires provide to him/her.<br></br>
										In this round knowledge will be tested regarding his basics in his electrical field.<br></br>
										He has to route the correct path for the instrumentation of electrical components.<br></br>
										Evenly his senses has to work out well for getting the correct path in the circuit.<br></br>
										If he/she determines the correct path for the working circuit to get the correct output given to him/her is promoted to the next round. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round III: (ELEC-‘TRIX’)</b>
                    <br></br> In this round the participant will be given with the electrical component parameters.<br></br>
										He/she has to connect them and solve that circuit for the given electrical theorem.<br></br>
										In this round knowledge will be tested regarding his basics in his electrical field of network theory.<br></br>
										If he/she solves the circuit correctly is promoted to the next round. <br></br>
										<b>Eg : </b> 10, 22, 68etc., 0.1mH, 0.01mH, etc., are given and has to obtain a 10KHz low pass filter. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b> 
                    <br></br>1. Only one participant is allowed at a time.<br></br>
										2. The decision taken by the faculty coordinator will be the final.<br></br>
										3. Any participants violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competition.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>For any queries mailus at "<i>sriharsha.kotaru@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    K.SHANMUKH SRIHARSHA
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 8500066667<br></br>
                    Email Id : sriharsha.kotaru@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </STOP_THINK>
            <E_QUEST>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>ELECTRIC  QUEST</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Round I: (pursuit)</b>
                    <br></br>1. In this round clue-based questions will be given to all the teams.<br></br>
										2. Various electronic components will be placed inside a room with number tagged on them.<br></br>
										3. The team has to identify the tagged components and answer the corresponding questions accordingly.<br></br>
										4. Teams will be permitted to next round on the basis of time management.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round II: (Rattling)</b>
                    <br></br> 1.The teams will be numbered and every team will be posed equal number of questions which include both positive and negative ratings.<br></br>
										2. At the end, teams with more number of points will be revealed and will be allowed to the final round. <br></br>
                    <b>Round III: Gaming round.  </b>
                    <br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>RULES:</b>
                    <br></br> 1. A team should comprise of max of 2 players. <br></br>
										2.  Players shall be promoted to the ongoing rounds on the basis of accuracy and time management.<br></br>
										3. The decision of the judges and the event coordinator will be final.<br></br>
										4. Cell phone usage is prohibited. If found the played will be immediately disqualified.  <br></br>
										5. In the case of tie between two teams tie breaker question will come into effect.<br></br>
										6. The teams found using unfair means will be disqualified. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>For any queries mailus at "<i>callmeteja999@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    M.TEJA<br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9440527695<br></br>
                    Email Id : callmeteja999@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </E_QUEST>
            <TEST_MEM>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>TEST YOUR MEMORY</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>ROUND 1:(Kwizz)</b>  
                    <br></br>1. In this round the participant will be asked general questions regarding basic electrical technology &amp; rudiments in electronic components.<br></br>
										2. Here participants will be divided into 2 members per team and each team will be given 10-15 questions the team which secures greater score will be promoted for next round.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 2:  (IDENTIFICATION OF SYMBOLS) </b>
                    <br></br>1. In this round the participants have to identify the number of symbols present in the given charts with in the specified time.<br></br>
										2. The team which identifies the symbols in less time will be qualified to next round <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 3:(SORT OUT)</b>
                    <br></br>1. The moto of this round is to arrange the different terms related to electrical &amp; electronics in a prescribed order.<br></br>
										2. Vivid stages present in those units will be written on cardboards and they will be scrambled.<br></br>
										3. The job of the participant is to set those stages in an order to get an ultimate output. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>RULES:</b>
                    <br></br>1.Each team should not exceed 2 participants <br></br>
										2.Electronic accessories should not be used <br></br>
										3. Any team violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competition <br></br>
										4. The decision taken by the Faculty and event co-ordinator will be final.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>For any queries mailus at "<i>charithsai3@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    S.SAI CHARITH
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9494363820<br></br>
                    Email Id : charithsai3@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </TEST_MEM>
            <FINGER_TWISTING>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="eee.php">EEE</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>FINGER TWISTING</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>THEME : </b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. Make Dreams Come True <br></br><br></br>
										In this event we are going to conduct 3 rounds.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND-1 : PICK IT UP </b>
                    <br></br>In this round the student will be asked to pick the specified value of electrical elements in a bunch.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND-2: TEXTING</b><br></br> 
                    1. The motto of this round is the participant will be given the audio clip and the paragraph.<br></br>
										2. The participants have to listen the audio clip and they have to type the paragraph given to them with in the specified time.<br></br>
										3. The participants who have completed the task in less time will be qualified for the next round.  <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND-3:RUBIX</b><br></br>
										1. In this the participant will be given a Rubix Cube.<br></br>
										2. They have to set the Rubix Cube so that they will get an equation related to Electrical Terminology.<br></br>      
                    <br></br>
                    <b>RULES:</b>
                    <br></br>  1. Only one participant is allowed to participate.<br></br>
										2. Accessories will be provided at the event. <br></br>
										3. For every event particular time will be provided.  <br></br>
										4. The one who violates the rules of the event will be disqualified.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>For any queries mailus at "<i>allaadithya3009@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    A.ADITHYA
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 7036057560<br></br>
                    Email Id : allaadithya3009@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </FINGER_TWISTING>
        </EEE>
        <CIVIL>
            <CIVIL_PAPER>
								 <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="civil.php">CIVIL</a>
                </NAV> 
							<TITLE>
								Paper Presentation
							</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
							  <b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
									<b>Topics For Paper Presentation</b><br></br>
									1. STRUCTURES<br></br>
									2. GEO TECHNICAL<br></br>
									3. TRANSPORTATION	<br></br>
									4. WATER RESOURCES<br></br>
									5. REMOTE SENSING AND GIS ENVIRONMENTAL<br></br>
								<br></br>
									<b>RULES:</b><br></br>
 									1) Team size should not exceed 2 members <br></br>
									2) Abstract should be in pdf or doc format <br></br>
									3) Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail <br></br>
									4) Interested teams are required to send their abstracts to <br></br>
									<br></br>
									<b>PRESENTATION:- </b>
									<br></br>1) Teams selected need to bring a soft copy &amp; the printed poster.
									<br></br>2) The poster should be of A3 size and the soft copy should be in PNG format<br></br><br></br>
									<b>Interested teams are required to send their abstracts to </b>
							</DESCRIPTION>
                 <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    N.Sai Venkatesh
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 7416630102<br></br>
                    Email Id : mr.sai2475@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </CIVIL_PAPER>
            <CIVIL_POSTER>
								 <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="civil.php">CIVIL</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
								<b>		Topics for POSTER PRESENTATIPONS: </b><br></br>
								1. STRUCTURES<br></br>
								2. GEO TECHNICAL<br></br>
								3. TRANSPORTATION	<br></br>
								4. WATER RESOURCES<br></br>
								5. REMOTE SENSING AND GIS ENVIRONMENTAL<br></br>
<br></br>	It is the presentation of projects. The students need to present their project  to judges followed by queries posed by judges. Judge will select best project and will be awarded.  In this event the participant has to come up with a problem faced by the people .<br></br>
<br></br>
									
<b>RULES:</b><br></br>
1) Team size should not exceed 2 members <br></br>
2) Abstract should be in pdf or doc format  <br></br>
3) Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail  <br></br><br></br>
<b> Interested teams are required to send their abstracts to gopichand.buddi94@gmail.com</b>
<br></br>
							</DESCRIPTION>
               <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                   B.Gopi Chand
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9963538180<br></br>
                    Email Id : gopichand.buddi94@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </CIVIL_POSTER>
            <CIVIL_PROJECT>
							 <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="civil.php">CIVIL</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>ARTS &amp; PROJECT EXPO</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
									It is the presentation of projects. The students need to present their project to judges followed by queries posed by judges.<br></br>Judge will select best project and will be awarded.  In this event the participant has to come up with a problem faced by the people.<br></br><br></br>
									<b>Topics for PROJECT EXPO: </b><br></br>
									1. STRUCTURES<br></br>
									2. GEO TECHNICAL<br></br>
									3. TRANSPORTATION	<br></br>
									4. WATER RESOURCES<br></br>
									5. REMOTE SENSING AND GIS ENVIRONMENTAL<br></br>
<br></br>
<b>									RULES:</b><br></br>
									1) Team size should not exceed 2 members <br></br>
									2) Project should be in pdf or doc format <br></br>
									3) Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail <br></br><br></br>
									<b> Interested teams are required to send their abstracts to vasavi.vas333@gmail.com</b>
							</DESCRIPTION>
              <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                   E.Vasavi
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9701251866<br></br>
                    Email Id :vasavi.vas333@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </CIVIL_PROJECT>
            <CAD_MANIA>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="civil.php">CIVIL</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>CAD MANIA</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Description:</b><br></br>
                    Today Designing is an essential  skill  for  a Civil Engineer.<br></br>
										<b>CAD MANIA</b> is the right place to prove your designing skills.<br></br>
										Face the rounds you come across successfully as per conditions given.<br></br>
										Become a best Designer.<br></br>
										This will help to enhance your drawing and designing skills by using AutoCAD software.<br></br>
										Tests on your basics regarding <b>AutoCAD software</b>.<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Procedure:-</b>
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 1: </b>
                    <br></br>A small entrance exam which consists of 20 objective questions regarding the basics of auto cad, building planning and construction.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 2:</b>
                    <br></br>Line diagram(plan) for the given building of given area on the spot.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 3:</b>
                    <br></br>Elevation of the given structure.
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Pre requisites:</b> autocad software.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    D.SUGUN KUMAR
                    <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9441416376<br></br>
                    Email Id : sugunkumar99@gmail.com
								</CONTACT>
            </CAD_MANIA>
            <STAAD_MASTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="civil.php">CIVIL</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>STAAD MASTER</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Description: </b> This event tests the skills of the participant to use STAAD Pro software efficiently.<br></br>The entire event is divided into 4 rounds as follows
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>PROCEDURE : </b> 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 1:</b><br></br>
                    Analysis of simple beams using STAAD Pro in specified time.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 2:</b>
                    <br></br>In this round the qualified candidates to participate in an online quiz.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 3:</b>
                    <br></br>In the final round the participants are given trusses to analyze using software within specific time.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Final round </b>
                    <br></br>The participants who completes the analysis within short period of time
                    <br></br>without any errors and warnings will be declared as the winners.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Pre requisites:</b> Staad Pro - Software<br></br>
                   </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    K.SRI HARSHA <br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9963353407<br></br>
                    Email Id : harshakommineni01@gmail.com
								</CONTACT>
            </STAAD_MASTER>
            <TECHNICAL_QUIZ_CIVIL>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="civil.php">CIVIL</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>TECHNICAL QUIZ</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    A quiz is a form of game or mind sport in which the players attempt to answer questions correctly.<br></br>
										A quiz is also a brief assessment used in education and similar fields to measure growth in knowledge, abilities or skills.<br></br>
										This event tests the basics of the students regarding various aspects and fields of civil engineering.<br></br>
										This quiz not only tests the clarity of basic concepts in chemical engineering and chemistry but also the analytical skills and logical reasoning skills essential for an engineer to analyse a problem critically and get quick solutions.<br></br>
										You could expect many new types of questions this time.<br></br>
										This edition will feature a whole array of stimulating new rounds and questions.<br></br>
										Do come and test your mettle here and attempt to get crowned champions of quizzing, or simply witness the coronation.<br></br>
										You are sure to learn tons of interesting facts.<br></br><br></br>
										<b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>civilproject@klusamyak.com</i>"</b>
								</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    S.MARIO NEELKAMAL<br></br>
                    Contact Number : 9573537689
								</CONTACT>
            </TECHNICAL_QUIZ_CIVIL>
        </CIVIL>
        <BT>
              <BT_PAPER>
  <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Paper Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
				Samyak is a National level technical fest conducted in KL University.
				This event is getting a great response from various leading technical institutions around the country. 
				We strongly support the students to conduct this event to enhance the knowledge sharing in the field of biotechnology to 
				cultivate new thoughts to kindle their minds. This event also helps the students to get a good organizing skill and enhance their 
				knowledge in the field of biotechnology.<br></br><br></br><b>Rules:</b><br></br>
1.	Every team may consist of 1 or 2 members. <br></br>
2.	Every participant should mail their abstract and full paper in one day advance to their presentation. <br></br>
3.	Paper should be in the specified format i.e., font: Times new Roman, fontsize:12 Line spacing 1.5,and neat page borders. <br></br>
4.	Every participant should present their paper through power point presentation.<br></br> 
5.	Participant should submit one hardcopy of their abstract &amp; paper on the day of presentation.<br></br>
6.	Every participant will be given maximum of 15 minutes for their presentation and 3 minutes for queries. <br></br>
7.	Negative points will be awarded if the time limit exceeds. <br></br>
8.	Judgment will be strictly based on their presentation skills, content and their innovative ideas.<br></br>
9.	The presentations will be divided into 4 categories (pharmaceuticals, proteomics, life sciences, genomics, Industrial)<br></br>
10.	 Judgment given by the judge is final.
							</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
				<b>Contact(s)</b><br></br>
				<b>Mail:</b> manikanta1051@gmail.com or manikantapadi72@gmail.com<br></br>
<b>Contact number: </b>7799438614
				</CONTACT>
            </BT_PAPER>
             <BT_POSTER>
							  <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>				
Samyak is a National Level Techno Management fest is going to be held on February 25 and 26.  
 It strongly supports the students to implement their innovative ideas and to produce their ideas 
in the form of oral, poster presentation. The main theme is to enhance the knowledge sharing in 
the field of biotechnology to cultivate new thoughts to kindle their minds. This event also helps 
the students to get a good organizing skill and enhance their knowledge in the field of biotechnology<br></br>
<br></br><b>Rules:-</b><br></br>
1. The Theme of the poster should be innovative, existing research ideas and performed <br></br>
2. Every team may consist of 1-2 members.<br></br>
3. Every participant should mail their full poster in one day advance to their presentation.<br></br>
4. DIMENSIONS: 2/3, 3/3, 3/4 feet.<br></br>
5.  Participant should submit one soft copy of their poster presentation.<br></br>
6. Judgment will be strictly based on purely on their presentation skills, content and their <br></br>
7. The presentations will be divided into 4 categories (pharmaceuticals, proteomics, life sciences 
genomics, Industrial) 
8. Judgment given by the judge is final.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
				<b>Contact(s)</b>
			<br></br>	
<b>Mail: </b>manisha.grandhi990@gmail.com
<br></br>
Contact number: 9581701832
				</CONTACT>
            </BT_POSTER>
						 <BT_PROJECT>
							  <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
					<TITLE>Project Expo</TITLE>
					<DESCRIPTION>		Students can consider this event as a welcoming opportunity to showcase their personified 
	ideas in the form of models. Any scientific or a technical marvel and its real time application 
	is a direct consequence of human intellect sprouted and nurtured by ones skills. These events 
	create such intentions for every student and make room for expressing their novel ideas. The 
	best project will be awarded.
	<br></br>
	<br></br><b>Rules:-</b><br></br>
	1.Team size should not exceed 3.<br></br>
	2.All the students are to be present along with their models at specified time. 
	<br></br>
					</DESCRIPTION>
					<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact(s)</b>
				<br></br>V.Vaishnavi<br></br>	
	<b>Mail: </b>vvaishu09@gmail.com
					</CONTACT>
				</BT_PROJECT>
					<BIO_TABULO>
              <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>BIO Tabulo</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
						The game Bio-tabulo consists of three rounds<br></br><br></br>
									<b>Round-1:-</b>   Match Me<br></br>
This Round follows by different Pictures related to science where we allot certain pictures to each player(around 6) to which are allotted ,The player should match them to the right one.
Time given: For 1 person-15 seconds and For 2-20 seconds<br></br><br></br>
									<b>Round-2:-</b>   Connection<br></br>
In this Round any picture will be shown to the players who were selected in the 1st round and the player has to write some related words on the paper connected to the shown picture and for that 15 seconds will be given
<br></br>Eg: if  banana is shown—Monkey—tree  etc..<br></br><br></br>
									<b>Round-3:- </b> Remember me if U Can<br></br>
The people who will be selected in the second round are allowed to play this round.In this round atleast 10 images related to science will be shown and for 15 seconds and turn offed after that and 20seconds time will be given for every player to reproduce that on the paper.The one who reproduces 1st will be the winner.
							</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
								<b>Contact</b><br></br>
							G.Siva Priya<br></br>spvarma.gajarla@gmail.com
							</CONTACT>
            </BIO_TABULO>
            <BIO_FABULA>
							 <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>BIO Fabula</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
							This event has 3 rounds<br></br>
									<b>1st round </b>consists of the following things word search<br></br>
The person should search maximum number of words in the given box .minimum time for this is 5 minutes. they have to find atleast 15 wors out of 20 words<br></br><br></br>
									<b>2nd round</b> consists of jumbled words<br></br>
In this round the person has to rearrange the letters from the jumbled word so that it have a meaning .there will be a time limit for this round too .they have to arrange atleast 10 out of 15 words<br></br><br></br>
									<b>3rd round </b>is jigsaw puzzles<br></br>
In this round the person has to arrange the picture from given jigsaw puzzle.the time for this is 15-20 minutes.
The winners will be short listed by the judges<br></br>
							</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact</b><br></br>
							M.Susmita<br></br>9949105020<br></br>susmitamallina@gmail.com
							</CONTACT>
            </BIO_FABULA>
					<PIN_IT>
							 <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Pin It!!</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
						In the present scenario listening or paying attention to every minute detail is very important. Two or four people can be participating in this game. One person would be blind folded as the other person gives the instructions towards the board. A picture will be drawn on board with a part missing in it which would be made out of cardboard plaster with double sided tape. All they have to do is to pin that part of the drawing on the board in the exact position where it should be. This game enhances the concentration and listening ability of an individual. 
									<br></br><br></br><b>Only 2 minutes will be given to each participant.</b>
							</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact</b><br></br>
							P.Vignya<br></br>vignyap61@gmail.com
							</CONTACT>
            </PIN_IT>
            <BLOOD_Group>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Blood Grouping</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    1. This is for all the people,who wanted to know their blood group.<br></br>
										2. Here we all knoe that there are  A ,B,AB  &amp; O blood groups in humans.<br></br>
										3. Some people may not have a chance till now to know their blood group.<br></br>
										4. Here  we have that chance to know our blood grouo with in 2 minutes.<br></br>
										5. so let us participate in this event to know our blood group.<br></br>
										6. The thing  we require is just a few  drops  of  your blood.<br></br>
										7. We will test your blood samples and tell what is your  blood  group ?    <br></br>
                    8. This will be  interesting. To know  your   blood group .....    so come and join this event .....<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    K.SRI VINUSHA<br></br>
                    Contact No: 8886518464<br></br>	
                    Email-ID: vinnu.sweety8216@gmail.com<br></br> 
                </CONTACT>
            </BLOOD_Group>
            <CRACK_CLUE>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Crack The Clue</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Crack the clue is the event in which the participants are given the housie tickets with empty boxes and the questions will be asked. They were supposed to paste the relevant answers in to those boxes within the given time limit.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>JUDGEMENT PROCESS:</b><br></br>
                    The participant who finishes his/her answers pasting in housie ticket at least time will be declared as winner.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    B.PHANEETH<br></br>
                    Contact No: 9666011113<br></br>
                    Email-ID: phaneeth.lion35@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </CRACK_CLUE>
            <SNAP_SHARE>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bt.php">BT</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Snap &amp; Share</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    This is for all the participants to showcase their photographic skills participants intrested can take a picture of any on going manufacturing process or working process of anylife sciences  related process industries.<br></br>
                    Example:  like    Fermentation /Agricultural/Chemical,  and this year we also includes hospitals , etc., in a eye catching manner.<br></br>
                    The participants need to post their photos on the facebook page named THIRD EYE<br></br>
                    (link:<a href="https://www.facebook.com/THIRD-EYE-406683629506470/?ref=hl" target="_blank"> https://www.facebook.com/THIRD-EYE-406683629506470/?ref=hl).</a> 
                    <br></br>
                    The no. of likes are considerd before the night (12:00 am) of the event the best photographs  which explains the actual process goin on in the industry will be credited.<br></br>
										Facebook likes also play a role in   judgement  and final decision will of judges .
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    T.J.SAI KIRAN<br></br>
                    Contact No: 8297495870<br></br>
                    Email-ID: tjsaikiran@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </SNAP_SHARE>
        </BT>
        <MECH>
            <MECH_PAPER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Paper Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
                    <b>Topic for paper presentation are: </b><br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Design solutions</b> <br></br>
                    Participants should emphasize on exploring new designs as well as modifications of present solution for development of new product. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>	Thermal solutions</b> <br></br>
                    Identification of suitable solution to the problems related to electrical energy in rural areas. Solutions for various routine actives in the villages such as safe and energy saving cooking method, design of small sized cold storage in dry units, energy consumption in the production of ornaments and black smith operations, etc.,<br></br>
                    solutions to other problems sources are encouraged.<br></br> <br></br>
                    <b>Manufacturing solutions through Micro ,Small and Medium Enterprises</b><br></br> 
                    Participants can present their ideas on micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMES)<br></br>
                    Including khadi and village enterprises which should contribute significantly to the Indian economy.<br></br>
                    Quality seed production, handicraft start-ups aimed at training man power to sustain the rich heritage, culture, and specialized skill can be presented.<br></br>
                    Any other production solutions also encouraged.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b> <br></br>
                    1.Team size should not exceed 2 members. <br></br>
                    2.Abstract should be in IEEE format. <br></br>
                    3.Selected participants will be informed shortly via e-mail. <br></br>
                    4.The team should submit 2 hard copies and 1 soft copy in CD (MS 2007 or higher version) containing their PowerPoint file (.ppt).  <br></br>
                    5.The hard copies should be typed in Font style-Ariel (size-12.line space-1.5,paper size-A4).<br></br>
                    6.Presentation should be in power point  <br></br>
                    7.Maximum no of slides per slide should not be more than 8 <br></br>
                    8.Any audio support if needed should be informed prior.  <br></br>
                    9.The teams will get 10 minutes to present their idea and 5 minutes for discussion. Judges decision will be final for the awards.  <br></br><br></br>
									<b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>chandracherry7@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>K.CHANDRASEKHAR <br></br>Contact number: 8374965811<br></br><i>chandracherry7@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </MECH_PAPER>
            <MECH_POSTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
										<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
									<b>Topic for Poster presentation are:</b> <br></br>
                    <b>Design solutions</b>  
                    Participants should emphasize on exploring new designs as well as modifications of present solution for development of new product. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>	Thermal solutions</b> 
                    Identification of suitable solution to the problems related to electrical energy in rural areas.<br></br>
                    Solutions for various routine actives in the villages such as safe and energy saving cooking method, design of small sized cold storage in dry units, energy consumption in the production of ornaments and black smith operations, etc.,<br></br>
                    solutions to other problems sources are encouraged. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Manufacturing solutions through Micro ,Small and Medium Enterprises</b> 
                    Participants can present their ideas on micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMES)<br></br>
                    Including khadi and village enterprises which should contribute significantly to the Indian economy.<br></br>
                    Quality seed production, handicraft start-ups aimed at training man power to sustain the rich heritage, culture, and specialized skill can be presented.<br></br>
                    Any other production solutions also encouraged. 
                    <br></br><br></br> 
                    <b>Note: Student can present poster on topics related to any field in mechanical engineering but presentation based on theme will be given priority in evaluation.</b><br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b> <br></br>
                    1.Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>  
                    2.The entire poster should be 40”X 60” in dimensions.  <br></br>
                    3.The board for poster is oriented in the "landscape" position <br></br>
                    4.Text should be readable from a minimum distance of 5 feet. <br></br>
                    5.Use a minimum font size of 18 points. <br></br>
                    6.Poster should be self- explanatory so that participants can discuss points raised by judges. <br></br>
                    7.The teams will get 7-10 minutes to present their ideas and 2 minutes for discussion. <br></br>
                    8.Selected teams will be intimated via e-mail or phone call.    <br></br><br></br>
									<b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>siddharthasivakoti@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact</b><br></br>S.SIDDHARTHA <br></br>Contact number: 9951316999<br></br><i>siddharthasivakoti@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </MECH_POSTER>
            <MECH_PROJECT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Project Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
                    <b>Topic for Project presentation are: </b><br></br>
                    <b>Design solutions</b>  <br></br>
                    Participants should emphasize on exploring new designs as well as modifications of present solution for development of new product. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>	Thermal solutions</b> <br></br>
                    Identification of suitable solution to the problems related to electrical energy in rural areas. Solutions for various routine actives in the villages such as safe and energy saving cooking method, design of small sized cold storage in dry units, energy consumption in the production of ornaments and black smith operations, etc.,<br></br>
                    solutions to other problems sources are encouraged.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Manufacturing solutions through Micro ,Small and Medium Enterprises</b><br></br> 
                    Participants can present their ideas on micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMES)<br></br>
                    Including khadi and village enterprises which should contribute significantly to the Indian economy.<br></br>
                    Quality seed production, handicraft start-ups aimed at training man power to sustain the rich heritage, culture, and specialized skill can be presented.<br></br>
                    Any other production solutions also encouraged.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>NOTE: Students can present projects on topics related to any field in mechanical engineering but presentations based on the theme will be given priority in evaluation.</b><br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b> <br></br>
                    1.Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>
                    2.Each presentation will be judged based on the judging criteria only	 <br></br>
                    3.The teams will get 10 minutes to present their idea, those exceeding time limit will not be eligible for the prize, regardless of the score. There will be a grace period of approx. 10-15 seconds before the penalty.  <br></br>
                    4.No reduction in score will be done for a presentation of less than 10 minutes.<br></br>
                    5.Presentation will be judged by the viewers and faculty members.<br></br>
                    6.Selected team will be intimated through e-mail.<br></br>
									  <br></br>
									<b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>maheswarm23@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>M.MAHESWAR<br></br>Contact number:8341917756<br></br>Email ID: <i>maheswarm23@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </MECH_PROJECT>
            <YOUR_TRUSS>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>YOUR TRUSS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Activity</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Participants need to solve problems regarding trusses and design an ideal truss with ice cream sticks to bear the given load .The best design will be awarded.<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rule:</b>
                    Individual participation
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>P.V.R.Kedaranath <br></br>Contact number: 9000503161
                </CONTACT>
            </YOUR_TRUSS>
            <TECHJAM>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>TECH JAM</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>ROUND 1:</b>
                    Round-1 of this event consists of JAM session i.e. just a minute in which Participant can choose a topic of their interest and speak on it for a minute.<br></br>	The best among them are selected for the second round.
                    <br></br><b>ROUND 2:</b>
                    In this round judges will be allotting a topic to the participants and they are asked to speak on the given topic. 
                    <br></br>Among these participants the best are selected for the final round.
                    <br></br><b>ROUND 3:</b>
                    This is the round of prelims. Participants will be given a questionnaire and they are asked to answer the questions with in allotted time.<br></br>The top scorer will be declare as winner
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>L.VENKATESH <br></br>Contact number: 9292952555
                </CONTACT>
            </TECHJAM>
            <TECHQUEST>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>TECH QUEST</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Description:</b>
                    <br></br>Tech quest seeks to bring young talents to take up the logical quests of mechanical engineering,
                    basic sciences of mechanical engineering and applications, technologies, working. 
                    This event will be a fun that unleashes your enthusiasm and interest towards mechanical engineering, spontaneity.<br></br>
                    <b>Event Details:</b><br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 1: Written Round</b>
                    This round stands a written format where participants need to answer to the questions based on basics of physics, mechanics, scientists and inventions. <br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 2: Written Round</b>
                    In this round you will be tested on your memory and knowledge on mechanical companies, products, technologies and applications. <br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 3: Final Round</b>
                    Depending on the entries some teams who qualifies round-1 and round-2 will be sent to the final round in which all the finalists will be facing the questions at a time. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rule:</b>
                    Team size should not exceed 4.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>B.CHANDU BABU <br></br>Contact number: 7075507828<br></br><i>burrichandubabu@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </TECHQUEST>
            <HOVER_CRAFT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>HOVER-CRAFT</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Description:</b>
                    <br></br>This event is focussed on the talent of young engineers in designing and developing a radio controlled hovercraft that is capable of travelling over land mud water ice and other terrains, where the hover will be tested for speed, stability and manoeuvrability.
                    Event details:<br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 1: Qualifier Round</b><br></br>
                    In this Round the Hover-Craft is examined if the craft is violating any rule, stability and control of the hover will also be tested and points will be awarded accordingly<br></br>
                    <b>ROUND 2: Challenger Round</b><br></br>
                    Here the Craft is to pass through a given track and the team to complete within the shortest time will be the winner. Load carring and stability of the hover craft will be tested. A payload of 50-100gms will be placed over the hover and set to complete the given track<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b><br></br>
                    1.Dimensions: Hovercraft size should not exceed box dimension of 80cmx40cmx30cm.<br></br>
                    2.Team size should not exceed 5.<br></br>
                    3.On-board voltage must not exceed 12V. <br></br>
                    4.Readymade kits or prefabricated hovercrafts will be eliminated<br></br>
                    5.Interchange of the hovercraft will not be permitted and if any team is found violating this rule will face elimination.<br></br>
                    6.Not more than 2 from the team are allowed to control the hovercraft.<br></br>
                    7.Judging criteria and area can be changed during the time of event depending on competition level.<br></br>
                    8.Only two motors are to be used in a hovercraft there is no limit on number of servo motors used.<br></br>
                    9.Hover should be capable to carry a load up to 100gms.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>AFTAB - 8977173359<br></br><i>mdaftabalikhan9@gmail.com</i>
                </CONTACT>
            </HOVER_CRAFT>
            <SOLID_WORKS>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mechanical.php">MECH</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>SOLID WORKS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Activity</b>
                    <br></br>Participants will be tested based on their fundamental knowledge in Solid works. Later they will be asked to design the given object within a time limit. Fastest and accurate design will win the race.
                    <br></br><br></br><b>Rule:</b>
                    Individual participation
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    Contact<br></br>Sk.Sameer <br></br>Contact number: 8712131565
                </CONTACT>
            </SOLID_WORKS>
        </MECH>
        <ECM>
            <ECM_PAPER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Paper Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
                    <b>SUGGESTED TOPICS:</b><br></br>
1 .Data mining and data ware housing<br></br>
2. Fddi-fiber distributed data interface<br></br>
3. Server virtualization.<br></br>
4. Embedded systems on internet of things<br></br>
5. Wireless optical communication <br></br>
6. Advances in magnetic field sensors<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b><br></br>
                    1) Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>2) Teams willing to participate should send their abstracts on or before<br></br>3) Abstract should be in pdf or doc format.<br></br>4) Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail.<br></br>5) Each team will be given 8min for presentation and 2min for queries.
<br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Presentation:</b><br></br>
                    1) The presentation should be in .PPT format .<br></br>2) Teams selected are required to bring soft copy and 2 hard copies of complete paper to the presentation.<br></br>3) Video clippings and voice recordings are not allowed. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judging Criteria</b><br></br>
                    a) Technical content of paper.<br></br>b) Presentation skills.<br></br>c) Answering Queries 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the students have to send their abstracts to "<i>paperecmsamyak2k16@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    M.V.S.N.SAI KUMAR<br></br>
                    8885215741<br></br>
                    vsnskm@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ECM_PAPER>
            <ECM_POSTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Poster Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Electronics:</b><br></br>
                    1. Nanotechnology and its importance<br></br>
                    2. Robots of the future<br></br>
                    3. Internet of things<br></br>
                    4. Wearable technology<br></br>
                    5. Evolution of processors
      <br></br>
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Computers:</b>
                                <br></br>
                    1. Hadoop and big data<br></br>
                    2. Internet of things<br></br>
                    3. Cybercrime, what it did to the world!<br></br>
                    4.  Evolution of networks<br></br>
                    5. Web design, where it is heading? 
                              <br></br>  
                                
                    <br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b><br></br>
                    1) Team size should not exceed 2 members.<br></br>2) Teams willing to participate should send their abstracts on or before samyak<br></br>3) Abstract should be in pdf or doc format.<br></br>4) Selected teams would be intimated through e-mail.<br></br>5) Each team will be given 8min for presentation and 2min for queries.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Presentation:</b>
                    Teams selected need to bring soft copies and 2 printed posters.<br></br>
                    The poster should be of A3 Size and the soft copy should be in PNG format. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judging Criteria</b><br></br>
                    a) Poster Making<br></br>
                    b) Content of the poster.<br></br>
                    c) Presentation Skills. <br></br>
                    d) Answering Queries<br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Poster Making:</b>
                                
                    The poster must be neat and legible.<br></br>
                    Apt background should be selected so that words are legible.<br></br>
                    A picture should speak the content of a 1000 words. 
                                <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Note: All the students have to send their abstracts to "<i>posterecmsamyak2k16@gmail.com</i>"</b>	
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    S.V.TEJESH KUMAR<br></br>
                    8106666202<br></br>
                    s.v.tejeshkumar@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ECM_POSTER>
            <ECM_PROJECT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Project Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Electronics:</b>
                    You need to display working mini projects on electronics, the best of them would be awarded. You can do projects on embedded systems, micro controller/processor etc. <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Computers:</b>
                    You need to display a real time mini project which can be put into use in the real world, the best of them would be awarded. You can do projects on web technologies or any application development etc. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Rules:</b>
                    Working models only.<br></br>
                    Ready-made kits are not acceptable.<br></br>
                    On-board, off-board source can be used.<br></br>
                    Applications of your model should be shown.<br></br>
                    Project may be movable or stable.<br></br>
                    Model should be unique.<br></br>
                    No two similar projects are allowed. 
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Judging Criteria</b>
                    Degree of Innovation- 20%<br></br>
                    Design &amp; Realisation-20%<br></br>
                    Performance-30%<br></br>
                    Content-20%<br></br>
                    Usefulness/Application-10% <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Expo:</b>All entries will be allocated exhibition space where the PROJECT  will remain throughout the day. Contestants are to man the exhibits at all times and should be available to answer questions from judges and members of the public. Prize winners will be announced at the end of the day of competition. Decision of judges if final. 
                    <br></br><br></br><b>Note: All the students have to send their soft copies to "<i>charles.finni123@gmail.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    T.CHARLES<br></br>
                    9441287252<br></br>
                    charles.finni123@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ECM_PROJECT>
            <!--<EXTERMINATOR>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Exter-Minator</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Are u good at rectifying error’s present in the given C/C++ code??? Here is an event for you. In this event a C/C++ code will be given to the participant. The participant should debug the error’s present in it in the given time limit. This an event which is used to test programming skills of the participant. The faster the participant the more he/she can bag!
                    <b>Note: For any queries mail us at "<i>ecmtechevents@klusamyak.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    
                </CONTACT>
            </EXTERMINATOR>
            <INTERCODERS>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Intercoders</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Teams are given programs in C/C++ and they are given time limit with in which they have to write the program in MATLAB which gives the same output or event vice versa. This tests programming application of the participant and how he/she can perform on various platforms!
                    <b>Note: For any queries mail us at "<i>ecmtechevents@klusamyak.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT></CONTACT>
            </INTERCODERS>
            <READY_INTW>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Ready for Interview?</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <i>
                        <b>Round 1:</b>
                    </i> This round is called this is a quiz round where you will be given some questions and you should be able to answer them differently with possible different solution. The winner will be on basis of how different your answer will be.
                    <i>
                        <b>Round 2:</b>
                    </i> Second round is based on situation. We will tell you the situation we are in and we will be expecting a probable different and flexible solution to solve the situation from you guys which will be the smart solution. 
                    This competition resembles a typical HR round in the interviews!! Participants getting ready for placements can test themselves here!! 
                    <b>Note: For any queries mail us at "<i>ecmtechevents@klusamyak.com</i>"</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT></CONTACT>
            </READY_INTW>-->
					 <ECM_CODEX>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
						 		<TITLE>CODE - X</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                  In this game the student will be given a set of codes or questions from different  various popular languages like C++,java. <br></br>
									There  will be errors in the given question and the student  need to pick the error and correct the code.the game also consists of writing the code for the given logic.<br></br>
									The one who pics the maximum number of errors and writes the code within the given time limit will be the winner.<br></br><br></br>
									<b>RULES</b><br></br>
									1.	Only one participant is allowed at a time (NO TEAM)<br></br>
									2.	Each participant is given 10 minutes to correct or built the code.<br></br>
									3.	Any team violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competition.<br></br>
									4.	Gadgets like mobiles are not allowed<br></br>
									5.	The decision taken by the faculity and event coordinator will be final.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    K.PRATYUSHA<br></br>
                    8897631819<br></br>
                    kopanati.pratyusha@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
					</ECM_CODEX>
					<ECM_TECHQ>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
						 		<TITLE>Tech-Quotient</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                  In this game the student will be given set of puzzles like the number puzzle,picture puzzle.It also consists of questions like aptitude,verbals etc.<br></br>
									The participant need to solve the given puzzle and submit. Student will be given appropriate requirements such as pen and paper. <br></br>
									The one who solves more number of questions in the given time will be the winner.<br></br><br></br>
									<b>RULES</b><br></br>
								1.	Only one participant is allowed at a time (NO TEAM)<br></br>
								2.	Each participant is given 10 minutes to correct or built the code.<br></br>
								3.	The decision taken by the faculty coordinator will be the final.<br></br>
								4.	Any partisipants violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competation.<br></br>
								5.	All the necessaries wiil be provided.<br></br>
								6.	Gadgets like mobiles are not allowed<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    P.SIVA NAGENDRAM<br></br>
                    7382790425<br></br>
                    sivapureti9316@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
					</ECM_TECHQ>
					<ECM_BRAINS>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
						 		<TITLE>Brain's Battle</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                 The game is regarding the quiz in electronic subjects like BDS,digital electronics etc.<br></br>
									The participant will be given set of questions and the one who answers all or maximum number of questions in given or less time will be the winner.<br></br><br></br>
									<b>RULES</b><br></br>
								1.	Only one participant is allowed at a time (NO TEAM)<br></br>
								2.	Each participant is given 10 minutes to correct or built the code.<br></br>
								3.	The decision taken by the faculty coordinator will be the final.<br></br>
								4.	Any partisipants violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competation.<br></br>
								5.	All the necessaries wiil be provided.<br></br>
								6.	Gadgets like mobiles are not allowed<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                  	 J.APARNA<br></br>
                    7416386048<br></br>
                    aparnajada@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
					</ECM_BRAINS>
            <DESIGNME>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Can You Design</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                In this game the student will be given a set of basic circuits and the student need to build the circuit accordingly in different tools like multisim, proteus, ride simulator etc. <br></br>
									The one who will design maximum number of circuits in the given time will be the ultimate winner.    <br></br><br></br>
									<b>Rules</b><br></br>
									1.	Only one participant is allowed at a time (NO TEAM).<br></br>
									2.	Each participant is given 10 minutes to correct or built the code.<br></br>
									3.	The decision taken by the faculty coordinator will be the final.<br></br>
									4.	Any partisipants violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competation.<br></br>
									5.	All the necessaries wiil be provided.<br></br>
									6.	Gadgets like mobiles are not allowed.<br></br>

								</DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    N.RAVI TEJA<br></br>
                    9603722431<br></br>
                    naraharisetti.raviteja@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </DESIGNME>
            <COMP_HUNT>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="ecm.php">ECM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Component Hunt</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    In this game the participant will be given a bunch of components and the participant must pick the appropriate  component mentioned by the event organiser. <br></br>
									Also a circuit may be given and the student will be asked to pick the appropriate components for the circuit mentioned . <br></br>
									The one who picks the maximum number of components in the given or less time will be the winner.<br></br><br></br>
	                   <b>Rules</b><br></br>
									1)	Only one participant is allowed at a time.<br></br>
									2)	The decision taken by the faculty coordinator will be the final.<br></br>
									3)	Any participants violating the rules of the instructor will be expelled from the competition.<br></br>
									4)	All the necessaries will be provided.<br></br>
									5)	Electronic gadgets are not allowed.<br></br>

                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b>
                    <br></br>
                    T.SAI PHANINDRA<br></br>
                    9000486636<br></br>
                    saiphani986@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </COMP_HUNT>
        </ECM> 
        <PETROLEUM>
            <P_PAPER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="petroleum.php">PETROLEUM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>PAPER PRESENTSTION</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
                    <b>THEME:</b> START-UP-STAND-UP-INDIA<br></br>
                    At present the situation for the development of unconventional oil and gas resources in our country is limited when compared to other countries. By increasing the efforts of developing these resources resulted in widespread economic benefits, including significant job creation, lower energy cost, revitalized manufacturing sector, new sources of government revenue and improved energy security for the nation. The idea behind it can bring substantial rise in environmental benefits by reducing the operational surface footprint, even the emissions of greenhouse gases is reduced. To improve this sector, the department of Petroleum engineering organizes this event expecting participants to come up with their ideas in this aspect. The work projected by the participants should contain a detailed explanation about the development of a particular resource. Participants are encouraged to come up with development ideas in different categories of unconventional resources that can be implemented in our country.<br></br>
									<br></br><b>Papers to be Emailed : pepaper4samyak2k16@gmail.com</b><br></br>

                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Faculty co-ordinator :- Mr. K.DINESH SREEKAR<br></br>
                    Student co-ordinator :- M.S.VARUN - 9441921317<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </P_PAPER>
            <P_POSTER>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="petroleum.php">PETROLEUM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>POSTER PRESENTATION</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<b>Theme:</b>
                    START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA. <br></br>  &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;Make Dreams Come True<br></br>
									<br></br>
                    Confronted with rocketing oil prices, to reduce fossil fuel consumption and greenhouse gas emissions to protect environment, developed and emerging countries are implementing policies encouraging biofuel production. The majority of production is based on technologies known as ‘first generation‘, using agricultural food produce to manufacture green fuels. This poster addresses the opportunities, challenges and risks related to the development of bio-fuels in the India where problems of fuel cost and pollution are most keenly felt. The participants are expected to show case their work based on alternative fuels, safety, health and environmental management, etc., while focusing on the theme of the event.<br></br>
									<br></br><b>Poster to be Emailed : peposter4samyak2k16@gmail.com</b><br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Faculty co-ordinator :- MR. K. RAJESH KUMAR<br></br>
                    Student co-ordinator :- B. SUBRAHMANYAM - 8985358975<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </P_POSTER>
            <JAM>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="petroleum.php">PETROLEUM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>JUST-A-MINUTE</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>JAM is JUST-A-MINUTE</b> The JAMmers are challenged to speak for one minute on a given subject without <b>“repetition, hesitation, or deviation“</b>.<br></br>
                    “Repetition” means the repetition of any word or phrase, although challenges based upon very common words such as “and” are generally rejected except in extreme cases. Words contained in the given subject are exempt unless repeated many times in quick succession. Skillful players use (sometimes obscure) synonyms in order to avoid repeating themselves. The term “BBC” maybe successfully challenged upon for repetition of “B”.<br></br>
                    “Hesitation” is watched very strictly: a momentary pause before resumption of the subject can give rise to a successful challenge, as can tripping over one’s words.<br></br>
                    “Deviation” means deviating from the subject, but has also been interpreted as “deviating from the English language as we know it”, “deviation from grammar as we understand it”, deviating from the truth, and sometimes even logic, although often leaps into the surreal are allowed.<br></br>
                    A JAMmer scores a point for making a correct challenge against whomever is speaking, while the speaker gets a point if the challenge is deemed incorrect. The game rewards those that make entertaining challenges, even if they do not speak for very long. An often rewarding time to challenge is a few seconds before the minute ends. Here, one could get a point for a challenge, not have to speak for very long, and get another point for speaking at the end of the minute. An extra point is awarded when a speaker speaks for the entire minute without being challenged.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Faculty Coordinator :- MR. D. NAGA RAMESH<br></br>
                    Student Coordinator :- <br></br>L. SAI TARUN (14008029)<br></br>
                    Ph No: 9705893154<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </JAM>
            <TECH_QUIZ>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="petroleum.php">PETROLEUM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Techincal QUIZ</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>GENERAL RULES</b>
                    <br></br>
                    1. Only team entries are eligible.
                    <br></br>2. A tram shall consist of maximum four persons.
                    <br></br>3. The questions shall be in the form of multiple choice, True / False statement, Specific answer question etc.
                    <br></br>4. The decision of quiz master will be final and will not be subjected to any changes.
                    <br></br>5. The participants shall not be allowed to use any electronic gadgets.
                    <br></br>6. Audience shall not give any hints or clues to the competitors.
                    <br></br>7. Replacement of any participant of a team is not allowed after registration.
                    <br></br>8. Teams selected for the final round will be allowed to give themselves an appropriate name related to the compitition by which they may want to be known.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>ELIMINATION ROUND-(In case more than 6 teams register on ......)</b><br></br>
                    <br></br><br></br>Each team would be given a set of question paper containing 25 multiple choice objective type questions.
                    <br></br>Time limit - 15 minutes.
                    <br></br>Only 6 teams would be selected for the STAGE ROUNDS.
                    <br></br>In case of tie between 2 or more teams, further 5 questions would be asked for the final selection.
                    <br></br>The selected teams shall have to appear for the final round.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>FINAL QUIZ  STAGE ROUNDS</b>
									<br></br><b>Round 1 :</b> A question would be asked to a team and if they are unable to answer it will be passed to the next team 
                    <br></br>Rounds 4 - <b>24 questions</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Each team would be asked 24 questions each. (Objective question with options)
                    <br></br>10 Marks for the correct answer.
                    <br></br>If a team cannot answer the question, they can pass the question and then the question would be farwarded to the next team.
                    <br></br>Answering time is only 30 seconds.
                    <br></br>Team discussion is allowed.
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 2 - Buzzer Round</b>- A question will be fired and the team who presses the buzzer first get to answer first -<b>6 Questions</b>            
                    <br></br>10 Marks for the correct answer and negative 5 marks foe the wrong or if team dosen't after they press Buzzers, - No farwarding
                    <br></br>Answering time is only 30 seconds.
              
                    <br></br><br></br>
                    <b>Round 3 : Rapid Fire Round</b> : -Each team will be asked 10 questions one after another in one minute time : <b>60 Questions</b>
                    <br></br>10 marks for the correct answer and negative 5 for the wrong answer.
                    <br></br>Answering time is only 3 seconds.
                    <br></br>Team discussion is allowed.
                    <br></br>If a team cannot answer the question they can pass for the next question. The question will not be farwarded to the next team.<br></br>
                    
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b>
                    <br></br>
                    Faculty Coordinator :- MR. G. MANOJ KUMAR<br></br>
                    Student Coordinator :-<br></br> 
                    Syed Sabeena (14008052)<br></br>
                    Ph No: 9550316429<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </TECH_QUIZ>
        </PETROLEUM>  
			 <BARCH>
             <PICKNQUICK>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="barch.php">B.ARCH</a>
							 </NAV>
							 <TITLE>PICK N QUICK</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                Pick and quick is fun based event. The event is to create a solid form or model using few selected materials in a stipulated time. It give us some fresh ideas which help us to motivate ones innovation.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                   <b>Contact</b><br></br>K.HARSHITHA<br></br>9581631384<br></br>harshithakuntumalla@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </PICKNQUICK>
           <PAPERQUIL>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="barch.php">B.ARCH</a>
                </NAV>
               <TITLE>PAPER QUILLING</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                A type of ornamental craftwork involving the shaping of paper, fabric or glass into delicate pleats or folds
Participants can make anything using the materials provided.

                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>S.VINUTHNA<br></br>8978389414<br></br>vinuthna98@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </PAPERQUIL>
           <LOGODESIGN>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="barch.php">B.ARCH</a>
                </NAV>
               <TITLE>LOGO DESIGN</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                Logo is symbol adopted by organization to symbolize its activity. It is a logical and creative way of show information in a simple manner through  a picture. Participants can choose any one of the given topics and design a logo  <br></br><br></br>
               <b>TOPICS:</b><br></br>ARCHITECTURAL LOGO<br></br>SOCIAL ISSUE LOGO<br></br>FASHION DESK
 
						 </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                     <b>Contact</b><br></br>G.PRANATHI<br></br>9246176761 <br></br>pranathi.gelli@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </LOGODESIGN>
            <NOTHINGTO>
                <NAV>
                    <a href="technical_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="barch.php">B.Arch</a>
                </NAV>
               <TITLE>NOTHING TO SOMETHING</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                Nothing to something is a competition which new things are created from scrap. It encourages the students to get new forms from the waste materials which we use in our daily life. Your ideas are not restricted. The materials are limited.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                     <b>Contact</b><br></br>K.VARSHINI<br></br>9100949098<br></br>katepalli.varshini32@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </NOTHINGTO>
        </BARCH>  
    </TECHNICAL>
    <LITERARY>
			<LIVE>
				<NAV>
						<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Live still poster(Act it Out)</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					The best way to make people understand is, by showing them how reality looks like and how the change looks like.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>Rules:</b><br></br>
					Participants may come in teams or can be made into teams instantly.<br></br>
					Each team will be given a topic then and there.<br></br>
					After 5mins of issue of the topic the team have to take their positions as characters in the poster depicting their topic.<br></br>
					The team should be still while acting their situation and only one person will be explaining their topic showing the team for 3mins.<br></br>
					The best still poster will be winning.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</LIVE>
			<MAKE>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Make A Story</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Words are how we think , STORIES are how we link.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>Rules:</b><br></br>
					1. Individual participation only.<br></br>
					2. Each participant will be picking up a paper from a lot comprising of 10 words .<br></br>
					3. Later each participant will be given 30mins time and using all those 10 words they need to develop a story (any kind ie. Fiction, comedy, tragedy , etc.)<br></br>
					4. The best will be winning!<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</MAKE>
			<ADZAP>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>AdZap</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Ad-zap is an event which can simply be called as an ultimate creativity test.<br></br>
					The event deals with recreating the ads that are today printed on the minds of the younger generation.<br></br>
					The participants will be forming groups of maximum 6 students and they will be given a product on which they will have to create an ad and enact it.<br></br>
					They however will be given time to think about the concept of the ad.<br></br>
					Each team can comprise of a maximum of 6 members and can constitute of members from different colleges too.<br></br>
					Each team will be given a maximum of 20 minutes time to answer questions on their product and convince the judges.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</ADZAP>
			<PRESIDENT>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>President for 5mins</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					A good leader can engage in a debate frankly and thoroughly, knowing that at the end he and the other side must be closer, and thus emerge stronger.<br></br>
					You don’t have that idea when you are arrogant, superficial, and uninformed. Nelson Mandela<br></br><br></br>
					<b>Rules:</b><br></br>
					1. You have to prepare a speech as the next PM candidate and show that what changes will you bring as a perfect leader.<br></br>
					2. Judgments will be done on the basis of Voting.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</PRESIDENT>
			<YOUTH>
				<NAV>
						<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Youth Sabha (debate)</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					With a view to strengthen the roots of democracy, inculcate practices of discipline, respecting views of others and to enable the youth of our country to have adept knowledge about the working of Parliament, KLU Youth Parliament (KYP) is an initiation to familiarize students with civics, constitutional policies and decision making in a Government Organizational Setup.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>Rules:</b><br></br>
					1.The conference is open for all university students .<br></br>
					2.QUESTIONNAIRE FOR THE PRELIMINARY ROUND.<br></br>
					3. Increasing involvement of major political parties in university elections - <br></br>
					Is it healthy for youth politics?<br></br>
					Lokpal/FDI/Nirbhaya bill/RTI.<br></br>
					Banning the media from showing smoking, drinking - will it have any impact?<br></br>
					3.Time Limit: 5 Min for each person.<br></br>
					4. Members in ruling party and in opposition will be decided on the chits drawn by the participant.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</YOUTH>
			<PICTURE>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                        
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Picture Perspective</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					"A picture is worth a thousand words” and at KLU,those words shall have the breath of life.
					This February, the multiple tongues hidden in the depths of every image, shall be unsheathed in a variety of perspectives and in every mode of articulation imaginable.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</PICTURE>
			<MOCK>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                        
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Mock Press Confer</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					This event is a mock rendition of a press conference wherein the judges would pose as journalists invited by the newsmakers (public figures ranging from politicians to scientists to writers, singers or film stars) to hear them speak and raise questions.<br></br><br></br>
					1. This event is a mock rendition of a press conference wherein the judges would pose as journalists invited by the newsmakers (public figures ranging from politicians to scientists to writers, singers or film stars) to hear them speak and raise questions.<br></br>
					2. The contestants are required to register upon which they would be given a choice between two public figures along with the agendas of the press conference. The agenda being the igniting spark of the press conference would be based on recent happenings and the participant would be expected to take up the stand as taken up by the public figure in question.<br></br> 3. The participants would be assessed on their flair for dramatics-a convincing portrayal of the character would help them win accolades. The contestant would also be graded on their ability to effortlessly imbibe characteristic personality traits of the public figure they are enacting in their demeanour. <br></br>*The contestants acting prowess and the intensity with which they vehemently defend the stand they have taken up would fetch those marks.<br></br>
					3. The event also invites active participation from the audience in the form of pertinent questions put up to the participants.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</MOCK>
			<WORDS>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                        
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Finding ALGO !!!</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Want to test your inner wordsmith? With organisers shooting words at you, one every five minutes,and you defending yourself by entwining those words into your story.<br></br>
					The words should come together to form a literary masterpiece.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</WORDS>
			<BLOCK>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                        
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Block-n-Tackle</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Block and tackle is your stage to have fun while talking for and against your own convictions.<br></br>
					Pick a topic and display how witty you can get switching sides on the same topic.<br></br>
					Waiting to be impressed by your wit, class and style!<br></br><br></br>
					<b>Rules:</b><br></br>
					1. On block prompt the participant talks for the topic and on tackle prompt the participant talks against the same topic.<br></br>
					2. Individual participation only.<br></br>
					3. A college can be represented by more than one participant.<br></br>
					4. Topics for the prelims will be non-technical.<br></br>
					5. The participant draws a lot in order to choose a topic.<br></br>
					6. Participants will be given 3 minutes to prepare on their topic.<br></br>
					7. They will be allocated 3 minutes to talk for and against the topic as per the judge’s prompt.<br></br>
					8. They will be judged based on the content, language and consistency.<br></br>
					9. The five best speakers will qualify for the finals.<br></br>
					10. Topics for finals will be current affairs and social causes.<br></br>
					11. The rules for prelims apply to finals also.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</BLOCK>
			<SPELL>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                        
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Spell Bee</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					A traditional literary event that no literary fest is ever complete without.<br></br>
					In a generation  where  language has degraded to the likes of “hw r u?”  and “im f9”, proper spelling is more important than ever.<br></br>
					Let your inner Grammar Nazi shine. This will be two levels with increasing difficulty.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</SPELL>
			<ORATION>
				<NAV>
					<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                        
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>ORATION</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Oratory is the masterful art.<br></br>
					The orator dominates those who hear him, convinces their reason, controls their judgment, compels their action.<br></br>
					For the time being, he is master.<br></br>
					It is an individual participation and the participant can deliver the orations of their own choice.<br></br>
					The best will be awarded.<br></br><br></br>
					<!--b>Note: All the members have to send their abstracts to "<i>ecepaper@klusamyak.com</i>"<br /-->
					Last date for submitting abstract is 20th February,2016
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</ORATION>
			<WALKING>
				<NAV>
						<a href="literary_events.php">Literary Events</a>                                         
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Walking Dictionary</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Vocabulary enables us to interpret and to express.<br></br>
					If you have a better vocabulary, you will have an unlimited vision and a bright future.<br></br>
					This event is held in two rounds with varying difficulties and the participant can be tested in any way – meanings of words or words for their corresponding meaning or synonyms for a word.<br></br><br></br>
						<!--b>Note: All the members have to send their soft copies to "<i>eceposter@klusamyak.com</i-->
					Last date for submitting abstract is 20th February,2016
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Contact :</b><br></br><br></br>
					Deekshatha<br></br>
					9640217515<br></br>
					deekshataa@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
					Savit Chandra<br></br>
					8712881963<br></br>
					savit.shahrukh@gmail.com<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</WALKING>
    </LITERARY>
    <MANAGEMENT>
       <BCOM>
            <INKARNO>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bcom.php">B.COM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>INKARNO</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>INKARNO</b> is an effort to promote true knowledge of business environment which includes different parameters like marketing, investment, finance, trading etc. the true spirit of this game show connected with stimulating activities and competitions which attract the best of students from across the nation, thus working towards a conglomeration of the most innovative brains from the core and crust of knowledge which gives a new direction and dimension to orthodox ways of thinking.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    P.Rajeev Meher<br></br>
                    9666581579<br></br>
                    meherrajeev95@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </INKARNO>
            <ENTREPRENEUR>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bcom.php">B.COM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>MR&amp;MS ENTREPRENEUR</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Innovation and talent are now the two trendy shoes that entrepreneurs wear. If you think you can fit in those shoes, here is your opportunity. You well be taken through a journey of three rounds. One out of which is a talent showcase round. Talents are not restricted to any terms and conditions. <b>SMART PEOPLE-BE THERE</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    B. Satvik<br></br>
                    9032925155<br></br>
                    bsatvik95@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </ENTREPRENEUR>
            <COMMERCIAL_NATIONS>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bcom.php">B.COM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>COMMERCIAL NATIONS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Business nations is an academic simulation where the participants wil be in the shoes of a “Delegate” of a country. The delegates are required to speak and debate on international business issues and abide by international business issues and abide by their foreign policies. Its time to get International... A debate taken to a higher level.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    D.Jagadeshwari<br></br>
                    7382014620<br></br>
                    sathyadabbiru555@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </COMMERCIAL_NATIONS>
            <BCOM_PAPER>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bcom.php">B.COM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>PAPER PRESENTATION</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    Economic development is the core issue in the development strategy of Indian government. It is believed to be the vehicle through which the problems like; poverty, illiteracy, unemployment, drinking water, sanitation, etc.
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    Avilash panda<br></br>
                    9493588049<br></br>
                    pandaavilash95@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </BCOM_PAPER>
            <INSTANTANEOUS>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="bcom.php">B.COM</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>INSTANTANEOUS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    A National level case study like never before! If you went a brain storming and absolutely nut crackling time, this is where you should be! Here, you won’t just solve cases you will debate on why other solutions are unfeasible. Get on your screens and submit your case online in the first round to embark on a “Not-so-cakewalk” journey to tackle some of the world’s trickiest cases. Those selected in the first round will move to the tougher bridge. <b>LET YOUR BRAIN EXERCISE!</b>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    M. Mounika<br></br>
                    7730974455<br></br>
                    mounikamovva95@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </INSTANTANEOUS>
        </BCOM>
        <HOTEL>
            <FRUIT>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="hotel_management.php">Hotel Management</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Fruit &amp; Vegetable carving:</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<image src="../asserts/images/events/management/hotel/fruit.jpg"></image><br></br>
                    <b>Note:</b><br></br>
•	Only one participant. <br></br>
•	90 minutes of time will be allowed. <br></br>
•	All the required material should be brought by participant only.<br></br>
•	 Only table will be provided for the display.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    PRANEETH<br></br>
                    9666339647<br></br>
                    praneethnadella@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </FRUIT>
            <BLIND_TESTING>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="hotel_management.php">Hotel Management</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Blind tasting</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<image src="../asserts/images/events/management/hotel/blind.jpg"></image><br></br>
                    <b>Note:</b><br></br>
•	Only one participant.<br></br>
•	Each participant has to identify the ingredient by tasting it.<br></br>
•	Participant is blindfolded.<br></br>
•	The contestant who can correctly identify the most ingredients win the competition.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    VENKATESH<br></br>
                    849998876<br></br>
                    jagarlamudivenkatesh12345@gmail.com<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </BLIND_TESTING>
            <RANGOLI>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="hotel_management.php">Hotel Management</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Rangoli Event</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<image src="../asserts/images/events/management/hotel/rangoli.jpg"></image><br></br>
                    <b>Note:</b><br></br>
•	This one is simple and would be helpful of for these less expertise in the Art.<br></br>
•	Only one participant with one helper is allowed.<br></br>
•	Try for a simple and a small Rangoli design with 4 x 4 Sq feet. <br></br>
•	The main features of Rangoli are using only five rangoli colours of your own choice.<br></br>
•	Time limit is 20 minutes.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    GOPINATH<br></br>
                    9700069657<br></br>
                    GOPINATHANIL89@GMAIL.COM<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </RANGOLI>
            <DESERT>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="hotel_management.php">Hotel Management</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Desert &amp; Main Course Plate Presentation</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<image src="../asserts/images/events/management/hotel/desert.jpg"></image><br></br>
                    <b>Note:</b><br></br>
•	Only 2 persons can participate as a team. Time allotted is 45 Minutes<br></br>
•	All the registered Candidates need to present the Pre-plated dishes in their own style. Cooking or Serving Material will not be provided by the Organizers.<br></br>
•	Organizers will provide only a table to present the dishes.<br></br>
•	Candidates have to arrange their own Presentation Materials<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    GYANESHWAR<br></br>
                    8885823585<br></br>
                    GANIG69628@GMAIL.COM<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </DESERT>
            <AROMAS>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="hotel_management.php">Hotel Management</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Aromas</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<image src="../asserts/images/events/management/hotel/aromas.jpg"></image><br></br>
                    <b>Note:<br></br><br></br>
Identification of spirits</b><br></br>
• Only one Participant is allowed for one registration.<br></br>
•	Participant has to identify name of the spirit by its aroma in 15min <br></br>
• Maximum identification will be announce as winner. <br></br>
•	Participant is allowed to smell the drink and need to identify the name of the drink.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    PATAN<br></br>
                    9581181243<br></br>
                    PRINCE88ROCKS92@GMAIL.COM<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </AROMAS>
            <TABLE_SETUP>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="hotel_management.php">Hotel Management</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Five course table setup</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
									<image src="../asserts/images/events/management/hotel/table_setup.jpg"></image><br></br>
                    <b>Note:</b><br></br>
•	Organization will provide only one table per participant.<br></br>
•	Participant need to get the required material on his Own.<br></br>
•	Only two participant is allowed for the one registration.<br></br>
•	Participant need to prepare a five course menu card with wine accompaniments.<br></br>
•	Pre-prepared cards are not allowed.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact:</b><br></br>
                    ESHWAR<br></br>
                    8185098956<br></br>
                    ESHWARPRASAD02@GMAIL.COM<br></br>
                </CONTACT>
            </TABLE_SETUP>
        </HOTEL>
        <MBA>
            <METRITA>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>METRITA</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme : </b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub><br></br>
                    In every conversation, there is always that one person who has an opinion on what stock everyone should invest in. Are you that one person? Do you have something more to say about your favourite company. This event will be all about stock market, trading in it, fluctuation in the market and how one person takes the decision for investing in one particular company. Come and experience the stock market trading.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    M.Ujwala<br></br>Phone No : 9133821630<br></br>Email : ujwala.satya@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
                    V.Gopi Chand<br></br>PhoneNo : 7396363153<br></br>Email : gopichandchowdare@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </METRITA>
            <TASWIQ>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>TASWIQ</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme:</b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub>
                    <br></br>
                    Participants will be products which have been failed in the market, analyse the reason for the failure and relaunch the product with your innovative ideas and rebuilt that particular product.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    B.Bhargavi<br></br>Email : b.bharthepudi@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
                    Y.Yagna Teja<br></br>PhoneNo : 9703772555<br></br>Email : yagnateja.y@icloud.com
                </CONTACT>
            </TASWIQ>
            <MANAV>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>MANAV SANSADHA</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme:</b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub>
                    <br></br>                
                  Participants have to show cast their skills all which are needed for HR manager. Participants must make a proper planning accordingly what the company requires that is a  right person in the right job with the right skills, at the right time.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    B.Bhargavi<br></br>Email : b.bharthepudi@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
                    Y.Yagna Teja<br></br>PhoneNo : 9703772555<br></br>Email : yagnateja.y@icloud.com
                </CONTACT>
            </MANAV>
            <EMPRESARIO>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>EMPRESARIO</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme : </b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub>
                    <br></br>                
                    While the debate rages on as to whether entrepreneurs are born or made, one thing cannot be disputed .Polishing certain skills can help you be a better entrepreneur. Whether you are already great at the following skills like communication, Branding, sales strategy from these areas will help you focus on for success. So this event will test you on your entrepreneur skills.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    Ch.Chaitanya<br></br>Phone No : 9948353563<br></br>Email : chaitanyasai651@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
                    P.Vamsi Krishna<br></br>Phone No : 7702218877<br></br>Email : deepthichandana.s@gmail.com 
                </CONTACT>
            </EMPRESARIO>
            <ONENA>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>ONENA GESTIONNAIRE</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme : </b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub>
                    <br></br>							
                    Excellent managers come in all shapes and sizes. They can be loud and quiet extroverted or introverted, Type A or calm .Their management style can be as unique as personalities .But while elements of personal style may vary. The aim of this event is to find out how he/ she demonstrate the skills, knowledge and talent of a good manager. It further tests on how he/she uses the strategies to solve a problem.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    V.Hema Abhinaya<br></br>Phone No : 9000748145<br></br>Email : abhi.vutukuri@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
                    M.V.Subhash Chandh<br></br>Phone No : 8099906148<br></br>Email : subhashchandh@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </ONENA>
            <QUIZARABLE>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>QUIZARABLE EINSTIENS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme : </b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub>
                    <br></br>								
                    Quizarable Einstiens is finest collection of business related knowledge; it aims to bring the best quizzing minds to provide a common platform where the twain will clash to win .It tests your logical thinking and overall knowledge.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    Aisha Rashid<br></br>Phone No : 7675848786<br></br>Email : aisha.rashid2022@gmail.com<br></br><br></br>
                    Vijaya jangala<br></br>Phone No : 7659966100<br></br>Email : vijayajangala100@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </QUIZARABLE>
            <KRAZY>
							<NAV>
                    <a href="management_events.php">Management Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="mba.php">KLU Business School</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>KRAZY KRITIKS</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION>
                    <b>Theme : </b>START-UP INDIA STAND-UP INDIA.<sub>Make Dreams Come True</sub>
                    <br></br>		
                  Krazy Kritiks is a general knowledge event. This event is purely based on the general knowledge which includes all types of general questions. The event consists of different types of rounds with different themes.This is a two days event which also consists of the personal interview round. Participants can check out their knowledge by this event.<br></br>
                </DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
                    <b>Contact</b><br></br>
                    S.Teja Amarendhar<br></br>Phone No : 8143573376<br></br>Email : Kunal4all@yahoo.com<br></br><br></br>
                    Priya kushwaha<br></br>Phone No : 9515310662<br></br>Email : Kshwhpriya@gmail.com
                </CONTACT>
            </KRAZY>
        </MBA>
				<LAW>
            <DEBATE>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="management__events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="law.php">LAW</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Debate Competition</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION></DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact :</b><br></br>
										G Sravya<br></br>
										7093357007<br></br>
										sravyaguda36@gmail.com
								</CONTACT>
            </DEBATE>
            <ELOCUTION>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="management__events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="law.php">LAW</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Elocution Competition</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION></DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact :</b><br></br>
									G Anvesh<br></br>
									8125524873<br></br>
									anveshguntur@gmail.com
								</CONTACT>
            </ELOCUTION>
            <LAW_QUIZ>
								<NAV>
                    <a href="management__events.php">Technical Events</a>
                    <div class="arrow">&#5171;</div>
                    <a href="law.php">LAW</a>
                </NAV>
                <TITLE>Quiz Competition</TITLE>
                <DESCRIPTION></DESCRIPTION>
                <CONTACT>
									<b>Contact :</b><br></br>
									B Rahul<br></br>
									9948419155<br></br>
									rahulboggavarapu@gmail.com
								</CONTACT>
            </LAW_QUIZ>
			</LAW>
    </MANAGEMENT>
    <SPECIAL>
			<TREASURE_HUNT>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Treasure Hunt</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					The treasure will be hidden and a set of clues directing to the treasure will be given to the participants. <br></br><br></br>
					<b>NOTE:</b><br></br>
					1. A maximum of 3 students are allowed per team.<br></br>
					2. Any kind of help from Non-team members will directly result in elimination.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</TREASURE_HUNT>
			<LAN>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>LAN Gaming</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					The games like <i>FLAT OUT, BLUR, FIFA, COD-CALL OF DUTY</i> and many more are installed in systems with LAN facility for the utilization of participants. Registrations will be done outside the Labs.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</LAN>
			<ANGRY>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Angry Birds</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					The Layers are formed by using thermocol sheets. The participant will be given a thermocol ball to play the game.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</ANGRY>
			<FUN_BASKET>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Fun Basket</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1.  PHOTO MANIA</b><br></br>
					Each player will be shown a photo and they should answer the question related to the photo.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2.  ABBREVIATIONS</b><br></br>
					Contestant should answer the given abbreviations, failing to do which ends the game. <br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. MAKE A STORY</b><br></br>
					We will show some photos to the players by observing them, players should be able to make up a story(relating to the photos shown).<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. DEFYING GRAVITY</b><br></br>
					One has to balance three balloons by standing inside a circle drawn around them, without crossing it.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. RUBIK’S CUBE</b><br></br>Participants will have to solve the Rubik’s cube in the shortest time<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</FUN_BASKET>
			<CHECK_YOUR_LUCK>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Check Your Luck</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. LOCKS</b><br></br>
					Locks with a bunch of different keys will be given, and one should identify the right key to unlock them.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. TRUST</b><br></br>
					The participant will have to control a remote car blindfolded. He /She will be given Guidance by his/ her friend.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. TARGET</b><br></br>
					Concentrate...aim...shoot... this is the way to win the game in which the participant will be given dart board and arrow.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. SCOOPING BALLS</b><br></br>
					The participant will be given a long stick with a net at one end. He / she should take balls out of a tub with the stick.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. MATCH THE CARDS</b><br></br>
					Participant will have to pick a card and has to match that card from the bowl that contains another set of cards.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</CHECK_YOUR_LUCK>
			<CARDS_COINS>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Cards and Coins</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. PENCIL AND COINS</b><br></br>
					A coin will be placed on the pencil and the player should hit the pencil so the coin falls on the given surface.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. MOUNT UP THE COINS</b><br></br>
					Pile up the coins to get the given amount in a limited time.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. SEPERATION ANXIETY</b><br></br>
					Place all the like cards together in stipulated time.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. PAPER AND  GLASSES</b><br></br>
					Make a paper bridge 5. GUESS ME: DAYS AND FESTIVALSwith glasses as the support and load the paper bridge with coins. The one who loads the highest number of coins is the winner.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. GUESS ME: DAYS AND FESTIVALS</b><br></br>
					Beautify the festival dates with coins. This can be done in various permutations and combinations.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</CARDS_COINS>
			<MAKE_SIMPLE>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Make It Simple</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. BLOW THE JOKER</b><br></br>
					Various Cards will be placed on glasses and the contestant should blow them till they find a joker.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. KABROOM</b><br></br>
					One contestant should hold a pile of glasses, and another has to throw balls to the one holding the glasses and he has to place the ball in the glass. The same is repeated till all the glasses have one ball and are piled.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. BALLONS AND GLASSES</b><br></br>
					Participants will have to blow the glasses with the help of a balloon.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. MIRROR MAPPING</b><br></br>
					A path is designed on a paper and it will be covered with a surface and the path will be shown in a mirror, the contestant should draw the line in the given path only seeing in the mirror.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5.  PUDDLE JUMPER</b><br></br>
					Three chances will be given to make the ball bounce once before it falls into a glass.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</MAKE_SIMPLE>
			<GRABE_THING>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Grabe A Thing</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Few rings will be provided to the player. The player should be able to throw the ring on to the object to win it.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</GRABE_THING>
			<PAPER_ROCKET>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Paper Rocket</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					To design and fly a paper rocket that will fly to a greater distance.<br></br>
					3 Rounds will be conducted<br></br>
					>> The paper rocket should be exactly thrown into a Tub.<br></br>
					>> The paper rocket should pass through the ring without falling down.<br></br>
					>> Time of the rocket in air.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</PAPER_ROCKET>
			<TOUGH_GOING>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Tought Gets Goings</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. POWER OF SILENCE</b><br></br>
					Contestant will be given a word or sentence or a movie name and that should be conveyed in mono actions.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. MULTI TASKING</b><br></br>
					Contestant should complete the given two tasks at the same time.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. BALL BOARD</b><br></br>
					The ball has to hit a board and fall into a basket placed at a distance.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. FILL THE BOTTLE</b><br></br>
					The participant has to fill the bottle by pouring the water with hands.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. TYPING MASTER</b><br></br>
					Participants will be tested for their texting abilities.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</TOUGH_GOING>
			<HARD_WIN>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Hard to win</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. TRICKY BRICK</b><br></br>
					There will be a brick in the bucket of water and the contestant should lift that up with help of two fingers.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. DARE TO DO</b><br></br>
					In this game, males and females are given different tasks<br></br>
					>> Males will have to braid the hair in first Round and in second round they have to thread a needle.<br></br>
					>> Females in first round they will blow Whistle and in second round they will have arm wrestling with other.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. NUMEROLOGY</b><br></br>
					Numbers will be given and the participants should be able to decode that into a sentence.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. MANTLE &amp; DISMATLE</b><br></br>
					Participant needs to pile up the given glasses into a castle and again you need to rearrange the glasses as given.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. BLOW THE BALL</b><br></br>
					Complete the given shape, by blowing the ball from glass to glass that are filled with water.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</HARD_WIN>
			<PHOTO_TALKIES>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Photo Talkies</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. SMART SELFIE</b><br></br>
					Contestant will be given a hint for finding a thing and in the given time they should find it out and click a selfie with that thing.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. SCROOP EFFECT</b><br></br>
					A list will be given and the contestant have to observe that for given time and pick the color as per instructions.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3.  LOGO QUIZ</b><br></br>
					A sheet of logos will be given and they have to be identified by the participant in the given time.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. ALIGNING PUZZLES</b><br></br>
					Contestant will be provided with set of puzzle pieces and in the given time one should complete the puzzle.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. SECTOR LISTENING</b><br></br>
					A list of things will be given and the contestant should sort the list in to their respective sectors in the given time.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</PHOTO_TALKIES>
			<FACE_CHALLENGE>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Face The Challenge</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					<b>1. DRAW THE TAIL</b><br></br>
					Draw a tail to the horse blindfolded in the given time.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>2. POPCORN THROW</b><br></br>
					Multitasking game where the participant, while eating a kernel of popcorn has to simultaneously throw a stone into a basket.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>3. BALLON BURST</b><br></br>
					Burst the balloons on the wall with your elbows!<br></br><br></br>
					<b>4. CATCH THE DUCK</b><br></br>
					The participant will be given a long stick with a net at one end. He / she will have to catch the ducks out of a tub with the stick in the given time.<br></br><br></br>
					<b>5. LIP TRACE</b><br></br>
					The first participant will have to wear the headphones and figure what the second participant speaks.<br></br>
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</FACE_CHALLENGE>
			<FOOT_POOL>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Foot pool</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					The pool table will be designed balls are provided and the contestants should kick the balls into the wholes.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</FOOT_POOL>
			<SAND_ART>
				<NAV>
					Special Events
				</NAV>
				<TITLE>Sand Art</TITLE>
				<DESCRIPTION>
					Sand art is the practice of modeling sand into an artistic form, such as a sand brushing, sand sculpture and sand painting. Using sand, you need to create an art.
				</DESCRIPTION>
				<CONTACT>
					<b>Special Events Coordinators</b><br></br><br></br>
					<b>Contact</b><br></br>
					Pavan<br></br>9491263344<br></br><br></br>
					Praveen<br></br>9885318171<br></br>
				</CONTACT>
			</SAND_ART>
    </SPECIAL>
    <CULTURAL>
			<NAV>
            <a></a>
       </NAV>
			
			<TITLE>RULES AND REGULATIONS OF INTER CULTURAL COMPETITIONS IN SAMYAK – 25th February, 2016</TITLE>
			<DESCRIPTION>
				<image src="../asserts/images/culturals.jpg" width="100%"></image><br></br>
				<b>REGISTRATIONS :</b><br></br>
1.The participants must reach the University by 9:00 a.m. sharp for registration on the day of the event.<br></br>
2. Particular Songs (for dance and vocals) to be played during the performance of the participants must be given to the concerned coordinators during the registration in a pen drive or a CD/DVD.<br></br>
3. All teams/members should be present at the NEW SEMINAR HALL by 11:00 a.m. sharp. Slot(s)will not be allotted for any team(s) in their absence at the time of call.<br></br>
4. ID cards are must. No member/group can register without ID cards.<br></br>
5. Best among all the performances in each category will get a chance to perform on the SAMYAK stage.<br></br><br></br>
				<br></br>
				To Know complete details <a href="../asserts/pdfs/cultural.pdf" target="_blank">Click Here</a>
			</DESCRIPTION>
			<CONTACT></CONTACT>
    </CULTURAL>
    <CINESCOPE>
        <NAV>
            <a></a>
        </NAV>
        <TITLE>Cinescope'16</TITLE>
        <DESCRIPTION>
						<image src="../asserts/images/cinescope.jpg" width="100%"></image><br></br>
            <b>COMPETITION IS FOR PROFESSIONALS AND NON PROFESSIONALS</b><br></br>
            Last Date for Registration : <b>FEB - 22nd</b>
            <br></br>
            Event Date : <b>FEB 25th and 26th</b>
            <br></br>
            <br></br>
            <b>Rule and Regulations :</b>
            <br></br>
            &#160;Judgement is consider separately for professionals and non professionals.<br></br>
            The film festival is open for professionals and non professionals.<br></br>
            The films should be sent on or before 22nd feb 2016.<br></br>
            Students and professionals are invited to participate in the following category:<br></br>
            &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Short film (Any genre) – Duration should not be more than 20 minutes for non professionals.<br></br>
            &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; – Duration should not be more than 30 minutes for professionals.<br></br>
            Entries for the short films should be submitted with their YouTube links and DVD along with the synopsis of the film and the list of team members in printed format.<br></br>
            Send the two DVD through Speed or Express Courier to the given Address.<br></br>
            Send the synopsis of the film and the list of team members.<br></br>
            Send the Participate name to the given mail address with the following details:<br></br> The title, running-time, phone number and contact email.<br></br>
            One person can send many entries with different theme, enclosed separately.<br></br>
            Short film should contain all the cast crew names.<br></br>
            Plagiarism will lead to disqualification.<br></br>
            Certificate will be provided for the registered participant.<br></br>
            Marks will be allotted on the basis of concept, screenplay, direction and picture quality.<br></br>
            <br></br>
            Send the Movie POSTER Along with DVD (Mandatory)
            <br></br>
            <br></br>
					<b><u>Selection:</u></b>
            <br></br>
            After screening, short listed short films will be intimated for the contest.<br></br>
            Declaration of winners is done by a judging panel comprised of industry professionals.<br></br>
            The decision of selection committee is final and no further correspondence will be entertained at any cost. Finalists will be notified by postal mail and/or email. The event management will use its best efforts announce the selected films, winners at the designated time, but will not be held liable for any unforeseen delays.
            <br></br>
            <br></br>
            <b>
                <u>Caution:</u>
            </b>
            <br></br>
            <b>Use of unparliamentarily language, religious representations, profanity and manipulative statements are strictly prohibited.</b>
            <br></br> 
            1. Entry pass is free for one person along with registered participant.<br></br>
            2. Registered student should send the college id along with registration form.<b>*</b>
            <br></br>
            <br></br>
            <b>*Mandatory</b>
            <br></br> 
            Online Registration link : <a href="https://goo.gl/fMa2y2" target="_blank">Find Here</a><br></br><br></br>
            <b>Send Courier to this Address:</b>
            <br></br>
            Y. Ayyappa<br></br> 
            Cinescope’16<br></br>
            Chalanachitra Club, KLUSO<br></br>
            Hobby Clubs, Indoor Stadium<br></br>
            K L University<br></br> Vaddeswaram-522 502<br></br>
            Guntur Dt.<br></br>
            Contact : <b>+91-9490299493</b>
            <br></br> 
            Email : <b>cinescope2k16@gmail.com</b>
            <br></br>
            <br></br>
            <b>Registration Amount :</b> Rs.500/-
        </DESCRIPTION>
        <CONTACT>
           <b>Registration Contact Details:</b>
            <br></br>
					 S N V S Satish - +91-949 287 9351<br></br>
            Y Ayyappa      - +91-949 029 9493
        </CONTACT>      
    </CINESCOPE>
</EVENTS>