<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<WORKSHOPS>
	<THREED-PRINTING>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>3D-PRINTING</TITLE>
		
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                    People who are attending 3D-PRINTING workshop are requested to bring their laptops along with them. <br></br><br></br></b>
			
			<b>Description:</b><br></br>			
			We see our world in 3D, then why don’t we print it in 3D? This workshop is on 3D printing which helps you to bring out your imagination and creativity. It’s difficult to express our ideas in 2D. So, here comes 3D Printing as an instant solution to implement our ideas in the real world. If imagination is your art, then 3D printing is your paint brush.<br></br><br></br>
			SAMYAK’16 brings forth a two day workshop on 3D PRINTING to create quick and cheap prototypes of products. This class is for inventors, creators, artists, entrepreneurs, SME’s and everyone who have intermediate computer skills and an idea of a prototype. You’ll gain exposure to the main phases of 3D printing including 3D scanning, 3D modelling, preparing the file for printing and finally <b>“THE 3D PRINT”</b>.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1200/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
			<br></br>
			<h3><b><i>All the Students Attending This Workshop are Requested Bring their own Laptop</i></b></h3>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			Md.Ishaakh Ahamad<br></br>
			9985544225<br></br><br></br>
			K.Srikar<br></br>
			7416684163<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</THREED-PRINTING>
	<ENGINE-OVERHAULING>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Engine Overhauling</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			Engine Overhauling is a two-day workshop that gives an opportunity to all the engine enthusiasts to take a wonderful ride through industrial workflow.
			The topics to be covered at the two-day workshop include - automobile component function, how a vehicle is conceptualized, designed, manufactured and various functions of engines, details on clutch, brake alignment/steering systems etc.<br></br><br></br>
			This workshop gives hands on experience on every sector related to engine designing.
			A detailed session of building each component of car along with a lecture on advancements of technologies in automobiles is an added advantage to the participants.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1350/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			V.Raghu Kalyan<br></br>
			7680899107<br></br><br></br>
			G.Chaithanya Baba<br></br>
			9492088861<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</ENGINE-OVERHAULING>
	<ICENGINES>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE> IC Engines &amp; CATIA </TITLE>
<DESCRIPTION>
In this workshop you will know about CATIA (Computer Aided Three-Dimensional Interactive Application) is a multiplatform computer-aided design/manufacturing software. CATIA supports multiple stages of product development from conceptualization, design, manufacturing and engineering. Here you will be taught how to design IC engine using CATIA, everything will be done from beginners’ level.<br></br>
In this workshop you will learn the entire function of IC engine with an exhibit, and further it will be continued by assembly and disassembly, “WHICH WILL BE EXPLAINED WITH AN ACTUAL BIKE ENGINE”.<br></br><br></br>
So, by this workshop you will gain knowledge on IC Engines &amp; CATIA.<br></br><br></br>
	<b>*Certificate of participation to every participant from IIT MADRAS and ARK TECHNOSOLUTIONS will be provided.</b><br></br><br></br>
	<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1000/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			Mahadev<br></br>
			8179710442<br></br><br></br>
			Anurag<br></br>
			9704794341
		</CONTACT>
	</ICENGINES>
	<RESPONSIVE-WEBATHON>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Responsive Webathon</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			Are you going to build your next web project and want to have a mobile friendly page for your readers?
			Now, more than ever, users are browsing th>e web via their mobile devices instead of their desktop computers.
			This class will teach you how to use various tools, such as CSS3 media queries, to build a single set of HTML that can be used in a variety of screen resolutions.<br></br><br></br>
			Students need to bring their laptop to the workshop as we will have hands on exercises, core team working sessions during workshop.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1200/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			M.V.S Manoj<br></br>
			7207867037<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</RESPONSIVE-WEBATHON>
	<CHARACTER-ANIMATION>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Character Animation</TITLE>
		
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                    People who are attending Character Animation workshop are requested to bring their laptops along with them. <br></br><br></br></b>
			Imagine bringing your favourite animated characters to life.
			Character animation is time and again constructed with creature animation where specialized animators bring life to realistic animals and creatures, such as dinosaurs and fantasy creatures.
			Character animators are often said to be actors with pencil (or mouse).<br></br><br></br>
			This workshop teaches you to design a character, rig the character and add a movement to the character.
			Movement involves developing facial expressions, lip movements on the face and body movement of the character.<br></br><br></br>
			So, <b>don’t miss this chance and do register at the earliest!!!!</b><br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1000/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br><br></br>
			<h3><b><i>All the Students Attending This Workshop are Requested Bring their own Laptop</i></b></h3>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			S.V.Praneeth<br></br>
			9160294004<br></br><br></br>
			A.Sai Bala Krishna<br></br>
			7207758704 <br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</CHARACTER-ANIMATION>
	<ANDROID-APP-DEVELOPMENT>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Android App Development</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			Android is an open source and Linux-based operating system for mobile devices such as smartphones and tablet computers.
			Android offers a unified approach to App development for mobile devices meaning developers need to develop only for Android, and their applications will be able to run on different devices powered by Android.
			This workshop helps you develop an Android App.
			<b>Register Now!!!</b><br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1200/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			R.K Akhil<br></br>
			8897598254<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</ANDROID-APP-DEVELOPMENT>
	<THUMB-PAINTING>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Thumb Painting</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                    People who are attending Thumb Painting workshop are requested to bring sheet, cloth, paint brushes and colors, pencil, eraser, scale, bowl along with them for the workshop. <br></br><br></br></b>
			An artist can win millions of hearts with his art. Such art comes with creativity.
			And what if that art is made using thumb? Interesting, isn’t it!<br></br><br></br>
			Thumb painting, one of the prominent arts, that brings out the creativity in you.
			These paintings were mostly used in historical artefacts and those techniques are implemented now-a-days. This type of painting is done by using thumb impressions.
			Thumb painting can be done on canvas or cloth.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1000/-.</i>(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			B Sai Krishna<br></br>
			9052619519<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</THUMB-PAINTING>
	<DSP-CONTROLLERS-IN-ENGINEERING-APPLICATIONS>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>DSP Controllers in Engineering Applications</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			DSP controllers are hybrid technology between micro controllers and the DSP processor modules.
			In the present day technology, the processors play a crucial role in the design of the systems.
			They have many advantages such as high processing speed, ease of multiplication operations etc.
			These processors are used in a wide range of industrial applications.<br></br><br></br>
			This workshop deals with the introduction to the controllers and its wide range of applications.
			The architecture and programming of Digital Signal Controller TMS320F2812 is explained along with hands-on experience on TI DSP kits.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1000/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			K.Prem Sai Krishna<br></br>
			9949625131<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</DSP-CONTROLLERS-IN-ENGINEERING-APPLICATIONS>
	<CATIA>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>CATIA</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                If possible people who are attending CATIA workshop are requested to bring their laptops along with them. <br></br><br></br></b>
			Career is all about upgrading and creation. Each one of us have the power of imagination and CATIA gives a shape to it.
			CATIA (Computer Aided Three-Dimensional Interactive Application) is a Computer-Aided Design (CAD)/Computer-Aided Manufacturing (CAM)/Computer-Aided Engineering (CAE) software suite written in the C++ programming language.<br></br><br></br>
			CATIA enables the creation of 3D parts, from various sketches and models, and tooling parts up to the definition of mechanical assemblies.
			The software provides advanced technologies for mechanical surfacing and also tools to complete product definition, functional tolerances as well as kinematics definition.
			This software has a wide range of applications for tooling design, for both generic tooling, mold and die.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1350/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact</b><br></br>
			A.Teja<br></br>
			7382589030<br></br><br></br>
			Ch.Bhanu Teja<br></br>
			8686224867<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</CATIA>
	<ENTREPRENEURSHIP>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Entrepreneurship</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                    People who are attending Entrepreneurship workshop are requested to bring their laptops along with them. <br></br><br></br></b>
			This workshop provides an introduction of being an entrepreneur.
			Participants will be able to recognize the fundamental features of the entrepreneurial mindset, behavioral skills, understand the central role of creativity and observation in identifying and developing entrepreneurial opportunities either as standalone businesses or social enterprises, or as part of a larger corporation.<br></br><br></br>
			Andhra Pradesh is a land of opportunities to implement entrepreneurship.
			The entrepreneurship buzz among students of Andhra is not that popular.
			So, <b>don’t miss the opportunity and grab the chance to be the next entrepreneur!!!</b><br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1300/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br><br></br>
			<h3><b><i>All the Students Attending This Workshop are Requested Bring their own Laptop</i></b></h3>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
		Contact(s)<br></br>
		<b>Lohith Bysani</b><br></br>Contact Number : 9908393310<br></br>Email Id : lohithbysani@gmail.com					
		<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</ENTREPRENEURSHIP>
	<BUSINESS-ANALYTICS>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Business Analytics</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                    People who are attending Business Analytics workshop are requested to bring their laptops along with them. <br></br><br></br></b>
			An ability that the young generation must essentially develop is Business analytics.
			This workshop acquaints you with the field of Analytics, builds your practical knowledge and skills, technologies and decision making practices that are essential for various applications of the same analytics in daily business decisions and challenges. 
			Business Analytics can help anyone think clearly about the situation in hand with an innovative approach to tackle the problem rather than giving up to the challenge. So what are you Waiting for…Grab your chance and register now!!<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1350/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
			<br></br>
			<h3><b><i>All the Students Attending This Workshop are Requested Bring their own Laptop</i></b></h3>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			G.Sai Manikanta<br></br>
			9949718032<br></br><br></br>
			R.Sai Kalyan<br></br>
			8125560504<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</BUSINESS-ANALYTICS>            
	<INTERNET-OF-THINGS>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Internet of Things (Ardeno)</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			<br></br><b>Note: 
                    People who are attending IOT workshop are requested to bring their laptops along with them. <br></br><br></br></b>
			The Internet of Things (IOT) refers to ever-growing network of physical objects, vehicles, buildings and other items that are embedded with software and Hardware which enables these objects to collect and exchange data.
			For example the IOT is used in various ways such as Medical and healthcare systems, building and home automation, Transportation and so on.<br></br><br></br>
			It creates opportunities for more direct interaction of physical world into computer based systems.
			IOT is expected to offer advanced connectivity of devices, systems, and services that goes beyond machine-to-machine.
			IOT is one of the platforms of today's Smart City and Smart Energy Management Systems.<br></br>
			So, <b>grab your chance and explore this emerging field?</b><br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1300/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact</b><br></br>
			L.K.S.Chandra Sekhar<br></br>
			7382124955<br></br><br></br>
			V.Sai Raviteja<br></br>
			9440998897<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</INTERNET-OF-THINGS>
	<PYTHON>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Python</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			Python is an exponent, object-oriented programming language.
			It offers dynamic data type, ready-made class, and interfaces to many system calls and libraries which can be extended using C or C++ language.
			Python is simple, easy to learn syntax emphasizes readability and hence reduces the cost of program maintenance.
			Its syntax allows programmers to express concepts in fewer lines of code.
			This makes the code short and flexible, and you lose the compile-time type checking of the source code.
			This program will inculcate confidence in the students by organizing expert talks and also working together on the same platform.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1200/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			Contact<br></br>
			A.Rama Hari Nandan<br></br>
			8686342424<br></br><br></br>
			R.Sai Kalyan<br></br>
			8125560504<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</PYTHON>
	<ETHICAL-HACKING>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Ethical Hacking</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			Hacking is an important tool of many national security agencies and companies.
			As new channels to store data and exchange of information has evolved, so does the need for cyber security.
			Ethical hacking is an important part of any organization’s arsenal against cyber threats.<br></br><br></br>
			SAMYAK'16 comes forth with a workshop to teach you just everything you need to know for effectively using hacking thereby protecting yourself against cyber threats.
			You will learn about TCP/IP fundamentals and operating systems like LINUX and UNIX.
			So what are you waiting for??<b>Grab your chance and register now!!!</b><br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1200/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			A.D Sandeep<br></br>
			8197838737<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</ETHICAL-HACKING>
	<NIRMAN>
		<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>Bridge Nirman</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			New technology is common but new thinking is rare.
			Bridge design is one of the oldest topics of civil engineering in which people will be exposed to various types of bridges and moving loads.
			SAMYAK’16, K L University is organizing a prestigious workshop in association with IIT MADRAS sponsored by ARK TECHNO SOLUTIONS.
			This training provides participants a unique opportunity to experience a hands-on-feel on civil engineering projects.
			Participants will design and fabricate their own bridge and test for the maximum loads.<br></br><br></br>
			The schedule of the workshop goes as follows:<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Day1:</b><br></br>
			1. A brief introduction about bridges, its parts, types and also study of truss bridge.<br></br>
			2. Case study on extra-ordinary bridges around the world.<br></br>
			3. Software demonstration. (PARTICIPANTS CAN BRING THEIR LAPTOPS)<br></br>
			4. Professionals will be in hand to provide ideas and suggestions in regard to bridge fabrication.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Day 2:</b><br></br>
			1. Approval of any outstanding design made by the participants.<br></br>
			2. Bridge fabrication.( KITS WILL BE PROVIDED)<br></br>
			3. Testing of bridges should be done by participants and inspection will be carried out by professionals.<br></br>
			4. Awards and certificates will be distributed in the evening.<br></br><br></br>
			Winners and runners of this competitive workshop will be qualified to the final round which will be held during CEA fest 2016 at IIT MADRAS.<br></br><br></br>
			Certificate of participation to every participant from IBCC India in association with CEA FEST 2016 IIT MADRAS and ARK TECHNOSOLUTIONS will be provided.<br></br><br></br>
			<b>COST : </b><br></br>
			All of this will be provided to you at a marginal cost of <i>Rs.1000/-</i>.(Excluding SAMYAK fee).<br></br>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT>
			<b>Contact : </b><br></br>
			P Aswin Prakash<br></br>
			7842702303<br></br><br></br>
			Dheeraj Mehta<br></br>
			9000453225<br></br><br></br>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</CONTACT>
	</NIRMAN>
	<CONTACTUS>
	<NAV>
			<a href="../workshops.php">Workshops</a>
		</NAV>
		<TITLE>CONTACT US</TITLE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
		<b>	G.Sai Manikanta<br></br>
			9949718032<br></br><br></br>
				R.Sai Kalyan<br></br>
			8125560504<br></br><br></br></b>
			<b>Email Id : samayakworkshops2k16@gmail.com</b>
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<CONTACT></CONTACT>
	</CONTACTUS>
</WORKSHOPS>